<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?><article><en><title>Testimonial - Quantum Pendant</title><content>&lt;p&gt;
	Grand Master Ricky Wong, Founder &amp;amp; Grandmaster Isshin Budokan Karate International.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table border=&quot;0&quot; cellpadding=&quot;0&quot; cellspacing=&quot;0&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td class=&quot;content&quot; valign=&quot;top&quot;&gt;
				&lt;table border=&quot;0&quot; cellpadding=&quot;0&quot; cellspacing=&quot;0&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td width=&quot;10&quot;&gt;
								&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
							&lt;td&gt;
								&lt;table border=&quot;0&quot; cellpadding=&quot;0&quot; cellspacing=&quot;0&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td class=&quot;content&quot; colspan=&quot;3&quot;&gt;
												This message of mine is not to make any medical claim but my testimony of the benefit I got from wearing Fusion Excel pendant. My name is Wong Sek Khar age 59 years and I am the founder and Grandmaster of Isshin Budokan Karate International (website: ibki.org)&amp;nbsp; and also the Grandmaster and Chief Examiner for Persatuan Karate Budokan Wilyah Persekutuan Kuala Lumpur.&lt;br /&gt;
												&lt;br /&gt;
												I have been actively teaching karate both locally and internationally until I suffered stroke in 2005. My life came crashing down and suffered depression because most evening I was not steady and easily become exhausted. I thought I could not perform and teach karate until I met Amy Woon and her husband on 19th September 2007. I was introduced to this miracle pendant. After wearing FusionExcel pendant, I gained back my confident and return to active karate.&amp;nbsp; Slowly I regain the mobility and strength of my right hand and limb and was able to perform my karate techniques with confidence.&lt;br /&gt;
												&lt;br /&gt;
												&lt;span lang=&quot;EN-ZA&quot;&gt;In Mid August 2008&amp;nbsp; I felt weakness on my left side and felt numb on my left hand. I quickly got myself admitted to hospital because I fear of getting my second stroke as doctors have told me before that the chances of getting second stroke is high if I do not take care. I was admitted to Selayang Hospital for two days and the CT scan showed sign of new stroke. After several examinations,&amp;nbsp; I was discharge. This time I didn&amp;rsquo;t have any sign of weakness on my left hand and limb and in fact the doctor was pleased to find that I was quite strong compare to other stroke victims.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
												&lt;br /&gt;
												I felt so much different from my first stroke in 2005. This time, I was able to walk unaided. One week after I was discharge from hospital, I was back teaching karate in one of my centre in Selayang.&amp;nbsp; This time I do not have to go for physiotherapy. FusionExcel pendant is really a miracle pendant and I am very grateful to Amy and her husband Mr. Woon and lastly not forgetting FusionExcel company and to Mr. Paul Ting, the man who brought in these pendants and give hope to people like me. To you wonderful people I would like to say thank you.&lt;br /&gt;
												&lt;br /&gt;
												&lt;strong&gt;MASTER RICKY WONG CREDENTIALS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
												&lt;br /&gt;
												Founder Grandmaster of Isshin Budokan Karate International.&lt;br /&gt;
												&lt;br /&gt;
												In early 70s&amp;rsquo; was appointed as&lt;br /&gt;
												- Senior Chief Instructor of Karate Association of Malaysia (KAM).&lt;br /&gt;
												- Trainer of Bank Negara Security Force.&lt;br /&gt;
												- Trainer of Pekeliling Police Field Force.&lt;br /&gt;
												&lt;br /&gt;
												In late 90&amp;rsquo;s was appointed as:&lt;br /&gt;
												- Trainer of Police Commandos in Andhra Pradesh, India.&lt;br /&gt;
												&lt;br /&gt;
												Chief Trainer of Golden Falcon Karate Association of United Arab Emirates.&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td width=&quot;18%&quot;&gt;
												&lt;img height=&quot;171&quot; src=&quot;http://fusionexcel.com/imgnews/ricky1.jpg&quot; width=&quot;104&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
											&lt;td align=&quot;center&quot; width=&quot;49%&quot;&gt;
												&lt;img height=&quot;171&quot; src=&quot;http://fusionexcel.com/imgnews/ricky2.jpg&quot; width=&quot;250&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
											&lt;td align=&quot;right&quot; width=&quot;33%&quot;&gt;
												&lt;img height=&quot;171&quot; src=&quot;http://fusionexcel.com/imgnews/ricky3.jpg&quot; width=&quot;222&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
</content><meta><description>FusionExcel pendant is really a miracle pendant and I am very grateful to Amy and her husband Mr. Woon and lastly not forgetting FusionExcel company and to Mr. Paul Ting, the man who brought in these pendants and give hope to people like me.</description><keyword>Grand Master Ricky Wong, Founder &amp; Grandmaster Isshin Budokan Karate International, Wong Sek Khar, Isshin Budokan Karate International, Persatuan Karate Budokan Wilyah Persekutuan Kuala Lumpur, CT scan, Mr. Paul Ting, Karate Association of Malaysia (KAM), Negara Security Force, Pekeliling Police Field Force, Golden Falcon Karate Association of United Arab Emirates.</keyword><robots>all</robots><author>klhunter</author></meta></en><bm><title>Testimonial - Quantum Pendant</title><content></content><meta><description>FusionExcel pendant is really a miracle pendant and I am very grateful to Amy and her husband Mr. Woon and lastly not forgetting FusionExcel company and to Mr. Paul Ting, the man who brought in these pendants and give hope to people like me.</description><keyword>Grand Master Ricky Wong, Founder &amp; Grandmaster Isshin Budokan Karate International, Wong Sek Khar, Isshin Budokan Karate International, Persatuan Karate Budokan Wilyah Persekutuan Kuala Lumpur, CT scan, Mr. Paul Ting, Karate Association of Malaysia (KAM), Negara Security Force, Pekeliling Police Field Force, Golden Falcon Karate Association of United Arab Emirates.</keyword><robots>all</robots><author>klhunter</author></meta></bm><chi><title>Testimonial - Quantum Pendant</title><content></content><meta><description>FusionExcel pendant is really a miracle pendant and I am very grateful to Amy and her husband Mr. Woon and lastly not forgetting FusionExcel company and to Mr. Paul Ting, the man who brought in these pendants and give hope to people like me.</description><keyword>Grand Master Ricky Wong, Founder &amp; Grandmaster Isshin Budokan Karate International, Wong Sek Khar, Isshin Budokan Karate International, Persatuan Karate Budokan Wilyah Persekutuan Kuala Lumpur, CT scan, Mr. Paul Ting, Karate Association of Malaysia (KAM), Negara Security Force, Pekeliling Police Field Force, Golden Falcon Karate Association of United Arab Emirates.</keyword><robots>all</robots><author>klhunter</author></meta></chi></article>