<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<article>
	<en>
		<title>Elvera Ruby G. Mariona, Becker Muscular Dystrophy.</title>
		<content>&lt;table background="img/testimonial_bg.jpg" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" style="color: rgb(0, 0, 0); font-family: Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; text-align: justify; background-color: rgb(238, 240, 252); " width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr bgcolor="#EEF0FC"&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td align="center" width="50%"&gt;
				&lt;img height="337" src="http://www.fusionexcel.com/imgnews/testimonial_elvera1.jpg" width="264" /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
			&lt;td align="center" width="50%"&gt;
				&lt;img height="337" src="http://www.fusionexcel.com/imgnews/testimonial_elvera2.jpg" width="264" /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td colspan="2" height="10"&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td class="content" colspan="2" height="10"&gt;
				Elvera Ruby G. Mariano, Fourth child of Rev. Claudio &amp;amp; Elsie G. Mariano. She was born on 31th January 1998, through Caesarian Section, weighing 10.4 lbs. Physically, she looked normal until Prep School. Age 3, She became prone to sickness. At age 7, we noticed that she gets tired easily just by walking short distances and also, her intellectual ability was left behind. We consulted a Pediatrician and the results said that she&amp;rsquo;s malnourished. From a born big baby, she grew weak and thin. In spite of being sickly, she was promoted to grade 2 but unable to read properly. 26th December 2006, Another Pediatrician gave an impression of her being malnourished. The diagnosis was the same with the others that we have consulted. As a mother, I have contested to the impression because many malnourished kids can walk properly, climb stairways fast, etc. unlike Elvera. She was given proper foods and attention but still, her situation got worse and led us to another consultation. We shared her condition to a teacher friend named Dr.Cleofe Palac. She conducted Behavioral and IQ Tests and found out that Elvera&amp;rsquo;s verbal areas of examination are equivalent to age 4 while her non-verbal areas are still in her age. With the results taken, they have deferred the result in muscular dystrophy that might be the cause of her intellectual deficiency. Further evaluation on muscular dystrophy has been recommended. In May 2007, we consulted a Neurologist. Along with the laboratory tests such as CPK muscles test, 2D Echo test, she was diagnosed of a very rare disease, the Becker Muscular Dystrophy. June 2007, she was given a medication of oral steroids and physical therapy three times a week. This helped Elvera to gain weight and improve her health but early this year, January 2008, we noticed that she can no longer go upstairs by herself. At that same month, Dr. Macalinao introduced to us the so-called &amp;ldquo;Quantum Pendant&amp;rdquo;, a pendant with scalar energy. He lent us the pendant for a night to test the effect. Surprisingly, the results were good. Elvera can go upstairs all by herself and walk longer distances without getting easily exhausted. We really praise God for the opportunity given to us by being beneficiaries of the Quantum Pendant. We pray that God will use this for the regeneration of her muscles.&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;strong&gt;- Elvera Ruby G. Mariona&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</content>
		<meta>
			<description>We really praise God for the opportunity given to us by being beneficiaries of the Quantum Pendant.</description>
			<keyword>Elvera Ruby G. Mariona, Becker Muscular Dystrophy, Rev. Claudio, Elsie G. Mariano, Caesarian Section, Prep School, Elvera, Behavioral, IQ Tests, Neurologist, CPK muscles, Dr. Macalinao, Quantum Pendant.</keyword>
			<author>KLHunter</author>
			<robots>all</robots>
		</meta>
	</en>
	<bm>
		<title>Elvera Ruby G. Mariona, Becker Muscular Dystrophy.</title>
		<content></content>
		<meta>
			<description>We really praise God for the opportunity given to us by being beneficiaries of the Quantum Pendant.</description>
			<keyword>Elvera Ruby G. Mariona, Becker Muscular Dystrophy, Rev. Claudio, Elsie G. Mariano, Caesarian Section, Prep School, Elvera, Behavioral, IQ Tests, Neurologist, CPK muscles, Dr. Macalinao, Quantum Pendant.</keyword>
			<author>KLHunter</author>
			<robots>all</robots>
		</meta>
	</bm>
	<chi>
		<title>Elvera Ruby G. Mariona, Becker Muscular Dystrophy.</title>
		<content></content>
		<meta>
			<description>We really praise God for the opportunity given to us by being beneficiaries of the Quantum Pendant.</description>
			<keyword>Elvera Ruby G. Mariona, Becker Muscular Dystrophy, Rev. Claudio, Elsie G. Mariano, Caesarian Section, Prep School, Elvera, Behavioral, IQ Tests, Neurologist, CPK muscles, Dr. Macalinao, Quantum Pendant.</keyword>
			<author>KLHunter</author>
			<robots>all</robots>
		</meta>
	</chi>
</article>
