<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?><article><en><title>FE Donates RM 10,000.00 to SAJA (School for Street Kids), Jakarta.</title><content>&lt;table border=&quot;0&quot; cellpadding=&quot;0&quot; cellspacing=&quot;0&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr align=&quot;center&quot; valign=&quot;top&quot;&gt;
			&lt;td colspan=&quot;2&quot;&gt;
				&lt;img height=&quot;299&quot; src=&quot;http://fusionexcel.com/imgnews/saja1.jpg&quot; width=&quot;448&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr valign=&quot;top&quot;&gt;
			&lt;td class=&quot;content&quot; colspan=&quot;2&quot;&gt;
				FE is proud to announce the donation of RM 10,000.00 to SAJA (Sekolah Anak Jalanan or School for Street Kids) Jakarta, at FE&amp;#39;s Achievers Recognition Dinner at Hailal International Club on Friday 29th August 2008. This donation on the part of FE means a lot to SAJA (the look on those children&amp;#39;s faces when they received the donation on the stage says it all. It is also the first time in their life they have ever had such a sumptuous dinner!) and is part of FE&amp;#39;s continues effort to help the less fortunate of society. FE hopes that FE&amp;#39;s successful leaders will follow suit and start contributing something back to help the less fortunate of society and help make this world a better place for all to live in!&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;br /&gt;
				SAJA was founded in 2001 with a vision &amp;quot;Every Child Has The Right to Equal Opportunity For Education&amp;quot; .The students at SAJA come from very poor families, such as trash scavengers and labourers,who live underneath the Gedong Panjang Toll Road, Nth Jakarta and surrounding areas. Currently the school has 110 students with 4 teachers and 1 principal. The school depends solely on donations from the public to operate.&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
</content><meta><description>FE Donates RM 10,000.00 to SAJA (School for Street Kids), Jakarta.</description><keyword>FE Donates RM 10,000.00 to SAJA (School for Street Kids), Jakarta.</keyword><robots>all</robots><author>klhunter</author></meta></en><bm><title>FE Donates RM 10,000.00 to SAJA (School for Street Kids), Jakarta.</title><content></content><meta><description>FE Donates RM 10,000.00 to SAJA (School for Street Kids), Jakarta.</description><keyword>FE Donates RM 10,000.00 to SAJA (School for Street Kids), Jakarta.</keyword><robots>all</robots><author>klhunter</author></meta></bm><chi><title>FE Donates RM 10,000.00 to SAJA (School for Street Kids), Jakarta.</title><content></content><meta><description>FE Donates RM 10,000.00 to SAJA (School for Street Kids), Jakarta.</description><keyword>FE Donates RM 10,000.00 to SAJA (School for Street Kids), Jakarta.</keyword><robots>all</robots><author>klhunter</author></meta></chi></article>