<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<article><en><title>Testimonial Of Alisa Simms, Singer, Queen Of Chicago Soul.</title><content>&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" style="color: rgb(0, 0, 0); font-family: Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 14px; text-align: justify; background-color: rgb(238, 240, 252); " width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td align="center" height="10"&gt;
				&lt;img border="0" height="252" src="http://www.fusionexcel.com/imgnews/cnbc5.jpg" width="336" /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="10" width="100%"&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td class="content" height="10" style="font-size: 13px; "&gt;
				The&amp;nbsp;Quantum Pendant&amp;nbsp;works great! I had so much energy today and usually by 11am. I&amp;#39;m nodding off at my computer but not today I was a live wire. I was able to work out much longer than I normally do which is only 30 minutes (today did 1 1/2 hour). Thank you so very much, I have been telling people at work about it and they are interested in purchasing one. Will need to talk with you more about that business opportunity.&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;br /&gt;
				As for my girlfriend she is just amazed that her knees have not been hurting like they normally do. She hasn&amp;#39;t felt relief in two years. She called me again today to say that she could&amp;#39;t believe her knees really have stop hurting. Which is a good sign. I don&amp;#39;t have any aliments that I know of but I can truly say it is doing something because my energy feels positive and different. Again many thanks!&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;br /&gt;
				PS Can&amp;#39;t wait to share this with my mom... Cheers!&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;strong&gt;- Alisa Simms, Singer, Queen of Chicago Soul.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</content><meta><description>The Quantum Pendant works great!I have been telling people at work about it and they are interested in purchasing one.</description><keyword>Testimonial of Alisa Simms, Singer, Queen of Chicago Soul, business opportunity, Quantum Pendant, energy positive, different, aliments.</keyword><robots>all</robots><author>klhunter</author></meta><alt_title></alt_title></en><bm><title>Hari Raya Open House 11th November 2006</title><content></content><meta><description>Hari Raya Open House 11th November 2006</description><keyword>Hari Raya Open House</keyword><robots>all</robots><author>klhunter</author></meta><alt_title></alt_title></bm><chi><title>Hari Raya Open House 11th November 2006</title><content></content><meta><description>Hari Raya Open House 11th November 2006</description><keyword>Hari Raya Open House</keyword><robots>all</robots><author>klhunter</author></meta><alt_title></alt_title></chi></article>
