<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<article><en><title>FE With General Dato' Kitti Ratanachaya</title><content>&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td valign="top" width="40%"&gt;
				&lt;img height="239" src="http://www.fusionexcel.com/imgnews/dato1.jpg" width="274" /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
			&lt;td class="content" style="font-family: Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 13px; color: rgb(0, 0, 0); text-align: justify; " valign="top" width="60%"&gt;
				FE would like to take this opportunity to thank General Dato&amp;rsquo; Kitti Ratanachaya for his support of FE. General Dato&amp;rsquo; Kitti was the former Thai Fourth Army Area Commander who was directly involved in the truce talks that ended the armed struggle of the Communist Party of Malaya leading to a peace accord between the CPM and the Malaysian Government on 2nd December 1989.&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;br /&gt;
				FE members who would like to read more about this historical episode of Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s history can purchase General Dato&amp;rsquo; Kitti&amp;rsquo;s book titled&amp;nbsp; &amp;ldquo;The Last Role of Chin Peng: The Communist Party of Malaya, Malaysia and Thailand&amp;rdquo; from FE&amp;rsquo;s HQ for only RM30.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;br /&gt;
				FE is indeed honored and privileged to be associated with a great man like General Dato&amp;rsquo; Kitti Ratanachaya!&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: center; "&gt;
	&lt;img height="843" src="http://www.fusionexcel.com/imgnews/dato3.jpg" width="653" /&gt;&lt;img height="1007" src="http://www.fusionexcel.com/imgnews/dato2.jpg" width="665" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content><meta><description>FE would like to take this opportunity to thank General Dato’ Kitti Ratanachaya for his support of FE. General Dato’ Kitti was the former Thai Fourth Army Area Commander who was directly involved in the truce talks that ended the armed struggle of the Communist Party of Malaya leading to a peace accord between the CPM and the Malaysian Government on 2nd December 1989.

FE members who would like to read more about this historical episode of Malaysia’s history can purchase General Dato’ Kitti’s book titled  “The Last Role of Chin Peng: The Communist Party of Malaya, Malaysia and Thailand” from FE’s HQ for only RM30.

FE is indeed honoured and privileged to be associated with a great man like General Dato’ Kitti Ratanachaya!</description><keyword></keyword><robots>all</robots><author>klhunter</author></meta><alt_title></alt_title></en><bm><title>Watch Video QP Wearer Long Drive Golf Champion Lance Reader!</title><content></content><meta><description>Watch Video QP Wearer Long Drive Golf Champion Lance Reader!</description><keyword>Watch Video QP Wearer Long Drive Golf Champion Lance Reader!</keyword><robots>all</robots><author>klhunter</author></meta><alt_title></alt_title></bm><chi><title>Watch Video QP Wearer Long Drive Golf Champion Lance Reader!</title><content></content><meta><description>Watch Video QP Wearer Long Drive Golf Champion Lance Reader!</description><keyword>Watch Video QP Wearer Long Drive Golf Champion Lance Reader!</keyword><robots>all</robots><author>klhunter</author></meta><alt_title></alt_title></chi></article>
