<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<article>
	<en>
		<title>FusionExcel Sponsors Surech Kuppusamy, World Class Mountaineer &amp; Quantum Pendant Wearer, To Summit K-2!</title>
		<content>&lt;table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" order="0" style="color: rgb(0, 0, 0); font-family: 'Times New Roman'; background-color: rgb(238, 240, 252); font-size: medium; " width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td align="left" valign="top"&gt;
				&lt;img height="232" src="http://www.fusionexcel.com/imgnews/surech1.jpg" width="353" /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
			&lt;td align="right" valign="top"&gt;
				&lt;img height="232" src="http://www.fusionexcel.com/imgnews/surech2.jpg" width="353" /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td align="left" valign="top"&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
			&lt;td align="right" valign="top"&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td colspan="2" valign="top"&gt;
				&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td align="left" valign="top" width="40%"&gt;
								&lt;img height="213" src="http://www.fusionexcel.com/imgnews/surech3.jpg" width="275" /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
							&lt;td class="content" rowspan="17" style="font-family: Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 13px; text-align: justify; " valign="top" width="60%"&gt;
								FE is proud to sponsor Surech Kuppusamy and the K-2 Challenge for Charity expedition and looks forward to FE&amp;#39;s flag plated on the summit of&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Mount K-2&lt;/strong&gt;, the world&amp;#39;s second highest and most challenging mountain to climb.&lt;br /&gt;
								&lt;br /&gt;
								Mount K2 (28,240 feet) is the 2nd highest mountain on Earth and has been referred to as the&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Gold Medal in Mountaineering&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;It is dramatically harder than Mount Everest, the highest mountain on Earth, and is considered the &amp;quot;Hardest Mountain on Earth&amp;quot;. Only 241 people have made it to the summit of K2 versus over 3000 that have summated Everest. Of these 241 individuals 60 have perished on their decent from the summit, making it the&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;most dangerous mountain on the planet&lt;/strong&gt;. K2 is dramatically steeper than Everest and has much more unpredictable and severe weather patterns.&lt;br /&gt;
								&lt;br /&gt;
								Mount K-2 Challenge for Charity expedition will commence on May 31, 2008. The team will converge in Pakistan where they will spend several days packing and organizing of 8000kgs of equipment which will be transported 18 kilometers up the Baltoro Glacier on the backs of the expedition team and the support crew. Broad Peak, the 13th highest peak in the world (8000meters / 25,000 feet), will serve as an initial acclimatization climb. The climb of Broad Peak is expected to take around 20days. The expedition will then continue up the Baltoro Glacier over several days to the Base Camp of K2. The following month will be spent establishing Camps 1-4 and transporting tents, gear, food, and oxygen to the higher camps. During this time the team will climb the equivalent vertical distance of having climbed the mountain from base to summit 3-4 times. There is generally only an 8-day window each year (last week of July and first week of August) during which the weather is suitable for a summit bid. Once in place at Camp 4 (26,000 feet), the team will await the opening of the weather and make their summit bid.&lt;br /&gt;
								&lt;br /&gt;
								Collectively the team members have the experience on major peaks, which includes Mount Everest, Cho Oyu, Manaslu, Shishapangma, Chogolisa, Ecuador, Masherbrum Nanga Parbat, Ama Dablam, and Broad Peak between them.&lt;br /&gt;
								&lt;br /&gt;
								&lt;strong&gt;CHARITIES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
								&lt;br /&gt;
								The K-2 Challenge for Charity project is done with the aim of reaching the summit of 8000 M peak and to raise funds for charities at the same time. 50 % of all cash contribution and all other contributions in kind will reach the beneficiaries listed below.&lt;br /&gt;
								&lt;br /&gt;
								&lt;strong&gt;KEM PENYAYANG KELAB KEMBARA&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
								&lt;br /&gt;
								MAS Backpackers-Kembara Club (BPKC), a sub-committee of Kelab Sukan MAS (KSM), organizes annual summer camps for underprivileged children. This project is done in co-operation with the Education departments in selected states. This year the summer camp scheduled to be held during the school holidays in August. The contribution is targeted to about 120 selected children.&lt;br /&gt;
								&lt;br /&gt;
								&lt;br /&gt;
								&lt;strong&gt;THE BUDIMAS CHARITABLE FOUNDATION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
								&lt;br /&gt;
								Was incorporated under the Trustees Act 1952 on September 14, 1998 and is under the royal patronage of our Queen, Duli Yang Maha Mulia Seri Paduka Raja Permaisuri Agong.&lt;br /&gt;
								&lt;br /&gt;
								Budimas&amp;#39; primary mission is to support projects that promote the welfare and well being of underprivileged children in Malaysia.&lt;br /&gt;
								&lt;br /&gt;
								Currently, Budimas is supporting up to 200 underprivileged children in three charitable homes in the country. These homes include Asrama Damai Anak-Anak Yatim in Kuang, Bethesda Children&amp;#39;s Mission Home in Rawang and Good Samaritan Home in Klang. Budimas help feed, clothe, care and support these children in every way possible to ensure they are given a future of love and hope. Underprivileged children have a right to happiness, hope, love and a home as much as any other ordinary child. Budimas is committed to giving the very best to these children and are driven by a philosophy of professionalism, high standards of governance and trust.&lt;br /&gt;
								&lt;br /&gt;
								&lt;strong&gt;THE CLIMBS &amp;ndash; Trip Report&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;
								&lt;br /&gt;
								&lt;strong&gt;MOUNT AMA DABLAM &amp;ndash; 2006&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
								&lt;br /&gt;
								Ama Dablam Expedition took place in the month of October and November of 2006. Mount Ama Dablam is situated in the heart of Khumbu Himal, Nepal Himalayas. This peak is the Nepal&amp;#39;s most coveted technical peak. It become famous among the best mountaineers of the world after Sir Edmund Hillary once declared it un-climbable. This peak poses a very high technical challenge because of its steepness. This peak was used as a preparation for K2 Challenge for Charity. Also this was the first Malaysian involvement in a serious alpine style climbing in the Himalayas. This peak was attempted without the use of supplementary oxygen and the expedition was concluded on the 09th November 2006.&lt;br /&gt;
								&lt;br /&gt;
								&lt;strong&gt;MOUNT CHO OYU &amp;ndash; 2007&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
								&lt;br /&gt;
								Mount Cho Oyu at 8201 meters is the 6th highest peak in the world and one of fourteen peaks which rise above the altitude of 8000 meters. Mount Cho Oyu is located on the border of Tibet and Nepal. The 2007 Expedition took place in the month of September and October of 2007. This peak poses a very high challenge of endurance due to its altitude. The climbers were also hit by the worst storm in the Himalayas since the last eleven years, during the climb. Because of the hurricane wind, the team tents and equipments were destroyed. The climbers had to continue with the remaining equipments and food supply. This peak was attempted without supplementary oxygen and the expedition was concluded mid-October of 2007. Also this was the first Malaysian involvement in the climbing of 8000-meters peak with no supplementary oxygen and the first on Cho Oyu.&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr valign="top"&gt;
							&lt;td height="82"&gt;
								&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr valign="top"&gt;
							&lt;td align="left"&gt;
								&lt;img height="188" src="http://www.fusionexcel.com/imgnews/surech4.jpg" width="275" /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr valign="top"&gt;
							&lt;td class="smallhead" style="font-family: Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 11px; font-weight: bold; "&gt;
								Mount Ama Dablam, 6856 M - 2006 Climb.&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr valign="top"&gt;
							&lt;td height="89"&gt;
								&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr valign="top"&gt;
							&lt;td align="left"&gt;
								&lt;img height="219" src="http://www.fusionexcel.com/imgnews/surech5.jpg" width="275" /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr valign="top"&gt;
							&lt;td align="left"&gt;
								&lt;span class="smallhead" style="font-family: Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 11px; font-weight: bold; "&gt;Coverage by The Star Cover News (Metro)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
								&lt;span class="smallcont" style="font-family: Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 11px; "&gt;Surech Kuppusamy , 28 has achieved his dream&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
								of climbing Ama Dablam in eastern Nepal. He&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
								wanted to tackle the peak after learning that&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
								the first person to climb Mount Everest,&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
								Sir Edmund Hilary, had dubbed it unclimbable&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
								&amp;ndash; VLADIMIR GOENKHA.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr valign="top"&gt;
							&lt;td height="101"&gt;
								&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr valign="top"&gt;
							&lt;td align="left"&gt;
								&lt;img height="185" src="http://www.fusionexcel.com/imgnews/surech6.jpg" width="275" /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr valign="top"&gt;
							&lt;td align="left" class="smallhead" style="font-family: Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 11px; font-weight: bold; "&gt;
								&lt;div align="left"&gt;
									Mount Cho Oyu, 8201 meters - 2007 Expedition.&lt;/div&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr valign="top"&gt;
							&lt;td height="93"&gt;
								&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr valign="top"&gt;
							&lt;td align="left"&gt;
								&lt;img height="216" src="http://www.fusionexcel.com/imgnews/surech7.jpg" width="275" /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr valign="top"&gt;
							&lt;td align="left" class="smallhead" style="font-family: Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 11px; font-weight: bold; "&gt;
								Surech at Cho Oyu 8201 meters - Peak.&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr valign="top"&gt;
							&lt;td height="86"&gt;
								&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr valign="top"&gt;
							&lt;td align="left"&gt;
								&lt;img height="227" src="http://www.fusionexcel.com/imgnews/surech8.jpg" width="275" /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr valign="top"&gt;
							&lt;td align="left" class="smallhead" style="font-family: Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 11px; font-weight: bold; "&gt;
								Damaged Tents After The Major Storm on&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
								Mount Cho Oyu.&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content>
		<meta>
			<description></description>
			<keyword></keyword>
			<author>KLHunter</author>
			<robots>all</robots>
		</meta>
		<alt_title></alt_title></en>
	<bm>
		<title>FE Welcomes Quantum Bracelet Wearer, Dato' Misbun Sidek, Coach And Former World Class Badminton Player!</title>
		<content></content>
		<meta>
			<description></description>
			<keyword></keyword>
			<author>KLHunter</author>
			<robots>all</robots>
		</meta>
		<alt_title></alt_title></bm>
	<chi>
		<title>FE Welcomes Quantum Bracelet Wearer, Dato' Misbun Sidek, Coach And Former World Class Badminton Player!</title>
		<content></content>
		<meta>
			<description></description>
			<keyword></keyword>
			<author>KLHunter</author>
			<robots>all</robots>
		</meta>
		<alt_title></alt_title></chi>
</article>
