<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<article><en><title>Read Quantum Pendant Testimonials of Prominent Thais!</title><content>&lt;table background="img/testimonial_bg.jpg" bgcolor="#eef0fc" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" style="border:solid 1px #000000" width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="25" valign="top" width="738"&gt;
				&lt;table background="img/buttonbg2.gif" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
					&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td class="header_title_white" height="25" width="738"&gt;
								&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;a name="10"&gt; &lt;span style="color:#ffffff; font-weight:bold;"&gt; Puan Sri Datin Rabitah Abdul Rashid&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="299" valign="top"&gt;
				&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" width="100%"&gt;
					&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="289" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
								&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td class="content" height="289" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
												&lt;div align="justify"&gt;
													5 months ago, I suddenly suffered from terrible &amp;quot;frozen shoulder &amp;quot;on both sides. The pain and agony was concentrated more on my right side and also on both sides of my neck. I experienced sharp pain like pricking needles on my right shoulder my back ached especially when sleeping at night. It was very uncomfortable and inconvenient for me lifting and using my right hand doing simple household chores, like hanging clothes, cooking simple dishes like fried rice, and most of all eating, putting food into my mouth. I tried many ways to cure the pains. One of them was applying the Far Infrared Ray Heat treatment.&lt;br /&gt;
													&lt;br /&gt;
													2 months ago I was introduced to this wonderful Quantum Pendant at a private dinner by a family friend of ours, a lawyer and businessman. Instinct told me this Quantum Pendant is unique and wonderful and possibly could cure me of my ailment. A few days after the dinner on this auspicious date, 23rd April 2007, I wore the Quantum Pendant and immediately I felt it working it was getting rid of my toxins. So I continued to wear it day and night and drank plenty of scalar-charged water by the Quantum Pendant. Sure enough my frozen shoulders and my backaches disappeared completely after 3 days. I am still proudly wearing the Quantum Pendant and drinking plenty of scarla-charged water and feeling great! Thank you Fusion Excel for this wonderful Quantum Pendant and the marvellous Quantum Sports Flask which I brought over to my family in London for instant charging.&lt;/div&gt;
											&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="10" width="740"&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="80" valign="top"&gt;
				&lt;table background="img/testimonial_bg.jpg" bgcolor="#eef0fc" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" style="border:solid 1px #000000" width="100%"&gt;
					&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="25" valign="top" width="738"&gt;
								&lt;table background="img/buttonbg2.gif" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td class="header_title_white" height="25" width="738"&gt;
												&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;a id="abdulkadir" name="abdulkadir"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#ffffff; font-weight:bold;"&gt; HASSAN BIN HJ. ADBUL KADIR CREDENTIALS. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="44" valign="top"&gt;
								&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td height="34" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
												&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
													&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
													&lt;tbody&gt;
														&lt;tr&gt;
															&lt;td class="content" height="34" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
																&lt;div align="justify"&gt;
																	&lt;p&gt;
																		HASSAN BIN HJ. ADBUL KADIR CREDENTIALS.&lt;br /&gt;
																		&lt;span class="product_black"&gt;- Manager/ Trainer of Selangor National Silat Association (2003).&lt;br /&gt;
																		- Trainer of Petaling District Silat Association, Awarded 6 Gold Medals.&lt;br /&gt;
																		- In 2000, Coached His Son to Become the Gold Medal Winner of SUKMA.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
																		&lt;br /&gt;
																		My name is Hassan, one month before the fasting month in 2006, I suffered from a serious backache. One day, when I was carrying 2 heavy barrels of petrol and walking towards my boat, I slipped on the steep slope. I was able to support my body with my left foot and did not fall down. But I had sprained my thigh and suffered from serious pain.&lt;br /&gt;
																		&lt;br /&gt;
																		Due to this incident, I was bedridden during the fasting month and could not celebrate the Raya festival. The pain continued for 2 months until I met Ah Tong who recommended the FusionExcel Quantum Pendant to me. After wearing the Quantum Pendant, things have changed for the better. Although the doctor advised me to undergo an operation but it was rejected as I have the Quantum Pendant now which has improved my condition significantly.&lt;/p&gt;
																&lt;/div&gt;
															&lt;/td&gt;
														&lt;/tr&gt;
													&lt;/tbody&gt;
												&lt;/table&gt;
											&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;table background="img/testimonial_bg.jpg" bgcolor="#eef0fc" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" style="border:solid 1px #000000" width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="25" valign="top" width="738"&gt;
				&lt;table background="img/buttonbg2.gif" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
					&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td class="header_title_white" height="25" width="738"&gt;
								&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;a id="mdmYap" name="mdmYap"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#ffffff; font-weight:bold;"&gt; Madam Yap Lee Yong, 32 Years Old. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="327" valign="top"&gt;
				&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" width="100%"&gt;
					&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="317" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
								&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td class="content" height="317" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
												&lt;div align="justify"&gt;
													&lt;strong&gt;Medical Problem: Gynecological Problem &amp;ndash; unable to conceive due to irregular and inadequate production of eggs. Eggs were also of low quality.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
													&lt;br /&gt;
													In 2001, after the doctor diagnosed my problem, he started me on 3 months of treatment to take medication in order to increase egg production. It was unsuccessful as there was no significant increase in egg production. I then tried artificial insemination 3 times but that was also unsuccessful. Finally, I decided to go through a test-tube pregnancy. I had a successful pregnancy only after the second attempt. I went through 3 years of sadness, stress, disappointments and pain not to mention the high medical expense to get a child. Finally, my daughter Wong Shi Qi was born on 29th November 2004. She is going to be 3 years old soon. The thought of going through another pregnancy was really frightening to me. I know I will have to go through another emotional, stressful ordeal not to mention the steep medical costs. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t decide in my mind if I would ever want to have another child.&lt;br /&gt;
													&lt;br /&gt;
													I was very shocked when I conceived in May 2007 after wearing the pendant and drinking the energized water for about 3 months. I understood from my doctor if I ever wanted another child it would be through another test-tube. In fact, my eggs have been saved in the egg bank in Subang Jaya Medical Centre, Malaysia. I didn&amp;rsquo;t have to go through the same tiresome and stressful procedures to get pregnant this time. It was so natural! My husband is so happy about having another child and so relieved that this time there&amp;rsquo;s no need to visit the Doctor more than necessary and hardly the same kind of expenses as before.&lt;br /&gt;
													&lt;br /&gt;
													We spent only RM 563 each for both by husband and myself to get a Quantum Pendant. What we received is a wonderful gift that is priceless &amp;ndash; the gift of a child!&lt;br /&gt;
													&lt;br /&gt;
													Thank you FusionExcel!&lt;/div&gt;
											&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="10" width="740"&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="131" valign="top"&gt;
				&lt;table bgcolor="#eef0fc" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" style="border:solid 1px #000000" width="100%"&gt;
					&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="25" valign="top" width="738"&gt;
								&lt;table background="img/buttonbg2.gif" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td class="header_title_white" height="25" width="738"&gt;
												&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;a id="KongSeong" name="KongSeong"&gt; &lt;span style="color:#ffffff; font-weight:bold;"&gt;Low Kong Seong, Table Tennis National Player (1983) and Participant World Cup Japan (1983).&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="95" valign="top"&gt;
								&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td height="85" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
												&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
													&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
													&lt;tbody&gt;
														&lt;tr&gt;
															&lt;td class="content" height="85" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
																&lt;div align="justify"&gt;
																	I was introduced to the Quantum Pendant by my good friend. At that time I was wearing magnetic bracelet and I was sceptical about the pendant. But to my surprise after wearing for two hours, I can feel increase in my energy and more alert. My friends also commented that I look much better and even my wrinkles have deminished. I found that I am calmer now and able to focus more clearly. I strongly recommend the Quantum Pendant to everyone!&lt;/div&gt;
															&lt;/td&gt;
														&lt;/tr&gt;
													&lt;/tbody&gt;
												&lt;/table&gt;
											&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="1"&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="10" width="740"&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="131" valign="top"&gt;
				&lt;table background="img/testimonial_bg.jpg" bgcolor="#eef0fc" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" style="border:solid 1px #000000" width="100%"&gt;
					&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="25" valign="top" width="738"&gt;
								&lt;table background="img/buttonbg2.gif" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td class="header_title_white" height="25" width="738"&gt;
												&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;a id="Edward" name="Edward"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#ffffff; font-weight:bold;"&gt; Edward Freeman. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="95" valign="top"&gt;
								&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td height="85" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
												&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
													&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
													&lt;tbody&gt;
														&lt;tr&gt;
															&lt;td class="content" height="85" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
																&lt;div align="justify"&gt;
																	&lt;p&gt;
																		When I first introduced to FusionExcel pendant, I was like most of the people, skeptical about the effects that were written about the product. But after listening to some real life testimonials from my associates, then I did some research over the internet. After watching some experiments conducted by Malik Noor on YouTube.com, I then visited the centre to test the experiment for myself. After the experiments I was totally amazed by its results that were as truthful as it is in the videos, thus l decided to purchase 5 units of FusionExcel Quantum Pendants for all my family member &amp;amp; grandparents.&lt;br /&gt;
																		&lt;br /&gt;
																		Being a full-time financial trader, the miracle FusionExcel pendant had brought me more energy to focus on my trades as well as to make critical judgments more rapidly. The most amazing result is that I have fewer yawns and snooze through out the whole day as compared to before. Every time before I take my bath, I will put my pendant into the bathtub to &amp;ldquo;charge&amp;rdquo; the water, as the charged water molecule became energized thus my bath will be more refreshing than ever. I would also &amp;ldquo;charge&amp;rdquo; all my drinking water, as for the result I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t need to wake up to re-hydrate my throat during midnight because the water molecule are adsorb more readily &amp;amp; retained longer in the body. My conclusion is that FusionExcel products are genuine &amp;amp; the benefits it will bring to the user is far more than anything stated in my testimonial, I&amp;rsquo;m truly thankful to FusionExcel for the benefits of health it gave to my family.&lt;br /&gt;
																		&lt;br /&gt;
																		Health has no price tag; FusionExcel is truly a great investment for your general well being.&lt;/p&gt;
																&lt;/div&gt;
															&lt;/td&gt;
														&lt;/tr&gt;
													&lt;/tbody&gt;
												&lt;/table&gt;
											&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="10" width="740"&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="131" valign="top"&gt;
				&lt;table background="img/testimonial_bg.jpg" bgcolor="#eef0fc" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" style="border:solid 1px #000000" width="100%"&gt;
					&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="25" valign="top" width="738"&gt;
								&lt;table background="img/buttonbg2.gif" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td class="header_title_white" height="25" width="738"&gt;
												&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a id="Ashley" name="Ashley"&gt; &lt;span style="color:#ffffff; font-weight:bold;"&gt;Ashley Choo, 32, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="95" valign="top"&gt;
								&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td height="85" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
												&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
													&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
													&lt;tbody&gt;
														&lt;tr&gt;
															&lt;td class="content" height="85" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
																&lt;div align="justify"&gt;
																	I heard about Quantum Pendant from a friend ever since I got it has worked very well for me. Quantum Pendant has given me energy; it has minimized my severe headaches due to being outdoors in the sun. Quantum Pendant has made me feel great, I am able to do much more than I could do. My days are longer because I have decided to use Quantum Pendant. Daily I wake up at 4.30am and most of my days end at 10pm , and occasionally even at 12.30am. I have no difficulty waking up the next day. I am really glad I discovered Quantum Pendant; I produce better results at work therefore resulting in more ideas and good feedback to solve problems. I have a clear mind, and I am glad Quantum Pendant has helped me to stay focused all through the day.&lt;br /&gt;
																	&lt;br /&gt;
																	I am able to do much more strenuous work physically as well as mentally. I have also discovered that Quantum Pendant helps to adjust muscle spasm. Recently I had a sprained shoulder, resulting in me having pain even at the neck, Quantum Pendant helped to minimize the pain and now I do not have the problem anymore. The pain was only there for 2 days.&lt;br /&gt;
																	&lt;br /&gt;
																	I also used to have constipation problem, now I no longer have this problem because Quantum Pendant has helped. I never used to be able to clear my bowels for more than 3 days, now Quantum Pendant has given me a 180-degree change now I clear my bowels twice a day. I feel much lighter in my abdomen.&lt;br /&gt;
																	&lt;br /&gt;
																	I am really happy I discovered Quantum Pendant because it has help me to be more focused at work, I feel healthier, and I am able to fight the flu germs. I used to be always sick with the flu but now no longer, all I can say is I have a healthy mind and body. Thank you FusionExcel for the amazing Quantum Pendant!&lt;/div&gt;
															&lt;/td&gt;
														&lt;/tr&gt;
													&lt;/tbody&gt;
												&lt;/table&gt;
											&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="10" width="740"&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="335" valign="top"&gt;
				&lt;table background="img/testimonial_bg.jpg" bgcolor="#eef0fc" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" style="border:solid 1px #000000" width="100%"&gt;
					&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="25" valign="top" width="738"&gt;
								&lt;table background="img/buttonbg2.gif" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td class="header_title_white" height="25" width="738"&gt;
												&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;a id="NicholasPua" name="NicholasPua"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#ffffff; font-weight:bold;"&gt;Nicholas Pua, 25 Years Old, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia. (Golfer). &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="299" valign="top"&gt;
								&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td height="289" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
												&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
													&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
													&lt;tbody&gt;
														&lt;tr&gt;
															&lt;td height="289" valign="top" width="200"&gt;
																&lt;img height="142" src="img/testimonial_nicholasPua.jpg" width="200" /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
															&lt;td width="15"&gt;
																&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
															&lt;td class="content" valign="top" width="503"&gt;
																&lt;div align="justify"&gt;
																	I am a full time golfer turning professional soon. I practice 8 hours daily. A friend of mine introduced the FusionExcel Quantum Pendant to me. After putting on the Quantum Pendant I find that it is able to help me to be more focused in my golf games. I feel more relax and more calm. Surprisingly I could even hit the golf ball to a further distance and with lesser effort. I also discovered that I am able to spend more time on my putting when I put on the Quantum Pendant. I no longer feel the backache which I normally do after 2 hours of putting. My flexibility have increased as well as the energy in my body as such I don&amp;rsquo;t feel that tired anymore after 8 hours of practise. It has also helped me to get good &amp;amp; sound sleep every night. With so many good &amp;amp; beneficial health features packed into one single product which &amp;lsquo;power&amp;rsquo; I was told could last more than 100 years makes the Quantum Pendant truly an Amazing &amp;amp; Value for Money product. I&amp;rsquo;ve recommended it to all my friends. Thank you Fusion Excel for this wonderful product which I believe will bring much help &amp;amp; aid to many people by improving their health &amp;amp; lifestyle.&lt;/div&gt;
															&lt;/td&gt;
														&lt;/tr&gt;
													&lt;/tbody&gt;
												&lt;/table&gt;
											&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="10" width="740"&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="335" valign="top"&gt;
				&lt;table background="img/testimonial_bg.jpg" bgcolor="#eef0fc" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" style="border:solid 1px #000000" width="100%"&gt;
					&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="25" valign="top" width="738"&gt;
								&lt;table background="img/buttonbg2.gif" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td class="header_title_white" height="25" width="738"&gt;
												&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;a id="Raymond" name="Raymond"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#ffffff; font-weight:bold;"&gt; Raymond Teoh, Proprietor of RGT Golf (Largest Retail Golf Store in Malaysia). &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="299" valign="top"&gt;
								&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td height="289" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
												&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
													&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
													&lt;tbody&gt;
														&lt;tr&gt;
															&lt;td height="289" valign="top" width="200"&gt;
																&lt;img height="115" src="img/testimonial_raymondTeoh.jpg" width="200" /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
															&lt;td width="15"&gt;
																&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
															&lt;td class="content" valign="top" width="503"&gt;
																&lt;div align="justify"&gt;
																	A friend introduced the FusionExcel&amp;#39;s Quantum Pendant to me. I was immediately impressed with the amazing demos. After putting on the Quantum Pendant, I discovered that my focus in golf games as well as at work was greatly enhanced. I was able to hit the golf ball to a further distance with the help of the Quantum Pendant and my swing and flexibility was amazingly improved.&lt;br /&gt;
																	&lt;br /&gt;
																	I usually get knee joint pains after four and a half hours of golf game but after wearing the Quantum Pendant overnight, the pains disappear completely. Sometimes playing golf under hot sun gives me headache but thanks to the Quantum pendant, the headache disappears too.&lt;br /&gt;
																	&lt;br /&gt;
																	The Quantum Pendant is truly an amazing product. It certainly improves a golfer&amp;#39;s game with the additional bonus of removing all those aches that accompanies long hours of golf game at the same time. I highly promote the Quantum Pendant to all my golf customers. Thank you FusionExcel for such a fantastic product.&lt;/div&gt;
															&lt;/td&gt;
														&lt;/tr&gt;
													&lt;/tbody&gt;
												&lt;/table&gt;
											&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="10" width="740"&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="335" valign="top"&gt;
				&lt;table background="img/testimonial_bg.jpg" bgcolor="#eef0fc" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" style="border:solid 1px #000000" width="100%"&gt;
					&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="25" valign="top" width="738"&gt;
								&lt;table background="img/buttonbg2.gif" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td class="header_title_white" height="25" width="738"&gt;
												&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a id="renaChong" name="renaChong"&gt; &lt;span style="color:#ffffff; font-weight:bold;"&gt;Rena Chong, Social Golfer. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="299" valign="top"&gt;
								&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td height="289" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
												&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
													&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
													&lt;tbody&gt;
														&lt;tr&gt;
															&lt;td class="content" height="289" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
																&lt;div align="justify"&gt;
																	I am a social golfer, however the past six months I&amp;#39;ve not played any game of golf due to busy work schedule. Recently, on 01st January 2007, my friends invited me for a golf game. I was quite reluctant initially, giving the excuse that I&amp;#39;ve not played for sometime and therefore may not be able to play well. However, just after playing a few strokes, my friends were surprised because I was able to achieve good shots. They asked me &amp;quot;how come?&amp;quot; Then I told them I have the FusionExcel Quantum Pendant in my pocket. I smiled and finally reveal to them the secret about the Quantum Pendant and its amazing powers.&lt;br /&gt;
																	&lt;br /&gt;
																	My friend who was wearing a Magnetic Bracelet asked me to let her try the Quantum Pendant. She tried the Quantum Pendant and confessed, &amp;quot;It really works!&amp;quot; She was able to hit the golf ball straight and further distance as a result of the Quantum Pendant.&lt;br /&gt;
																	&lt;br /&gt;
																	In the month of February 2007, I went for a golf game in Kota Kinabalu, Sabah. Usually the furthest distance I could achieve was about 120 meter. That day I was able to achieve a distance of 180 meter. The caddie recommended that I hit the golf ball to the side to avoid the pond. However, I took the challenge and hit the ball straight over the pond. The caddie was surprised and remarked to me, &amp;quot;Puan, today you banyak bagus!&amp;quot;. I replied to him that it was not me but the amazing Quantum Pendant that provided the extra help.&lt;br /&gt;
																	&lt;br /&gt;
																	I have an acute backache problem for few years. I spent about RM 100 each month to buy medicinal plaster made in Taiwan to help relieve the pain. Now, after putting on the Quantum Pendant, my acute backache is 95% gone! Also I can save RM 1,200 yearly now as I no longer have to buy the medicinal plaster. I also use the Quantum Pendant to &amp;#39;charge&amp;#39; the drinking water overnight. After drinking the &amp;#39;charged&amp;#39; water, I could feel the &amp;#39;winds&amp;#39; leaving my body.&lt;br /&gt;
																	&lt;br /&gt;
																	Also I have migraine problem for 20 years. Recently, I had a relapse of migraine attack in September 2006. I usually get this attack every 3 to 4 months. After putting on the Quantum Pendant in November 2006, amazingly I&amp;#39;ve not have a single migraine attack for the past 4 months and my high blood pressure also have dropped.&lt;/div&gt;
															&lt;/td&gt;
														&lt;/tr&gt;
													&lt;/tbody&gt;
												&lt;/table&gt;
											&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="10" width="740"&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="267" valign="top"&gt;
				&lt;table bgcolor="#eef0fc" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" style="border:solid 1px #000000" width="100%"&gt;
					&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="25" valign="top" width="738"&gt;
								&lt;table background="img/buttonbg2.gif" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td class="header_title_white" height="25" width="738"&gt;
												&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;a id="renaFather" name="renaFather"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#ffffff; font-weight:bold;"&gt; Rena Chong&amp;#39;s Father-in-law. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="231" valign="top"&gt;
								&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td height="221" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
												&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
													&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
													&lt;tbody&gt;
														&lt;tr&gt;
															&lt;td class="content" height="221" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
																&lt;div align="justify"&gt;
																	My 89 years old father-in-law has swollen feet and joint pain problem. One day I asked him to try the Quantum Pendant as it may help him. Usually he refuses to try any other health product that I buy for him. However, this time he tried the Quantum Pendant since he didn&amp;#39;t have to consume anything. After 2 days, he still didn&amp;#39;t return it to me, when I enquired what is his opinion about the Quantum Pendant. He said, &amp;ldquo;Can I keep it?&amp;rdquo; I smiled as he shared with me how the Quantum Pendant has relieved him of his joint pains and also reduce his swollen feet.&lt;br /&gt;
																	&lt;br /&gt;
																	No words can express the joy it brings to see your own loved ones being relieved of their pains when they have suffered for so many years especially when it is within your power or ability to do so. Previously, not much could be done to help my father-in-law to ease his suffering. Now with the Quantum Pendant, this is possible.&lt;br /&gt;
																	&lt;br /&gt;
																	Thank you FusionExcel for this wonderful product.&lt;/div&gt;
															&lt;/td&gt;
														&lt;/tr&gt;
													&lt;/tbody&gt;
												&lt;/table&gt;
											&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="10" width="740"&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td valign="top"&gt;
				&lt;table bgcolor="#eef0fc" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" style="border:solid 1px #000000" width="100%"&gt;
					&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="25" valign="top" width="738"&gt;
								&lt;table background="img/buttonbg2.gif" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td class="header_title_white" height="25" width="738"&gt;
												&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;a id="aubrey" name="aubrey"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#ffffff; font-weight:bold;"&gt; Aubrey Swee Seet Peng, FitnessFirst Personal Trainer, Group Exercise Instructor. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td valign="top"&gt;
								&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td valign="top" width="718"&gt;
												&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
													&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
													&lt;tbody&gt;
														&lt;tr&gt;
															&lt;td class="content" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
																&lt;div align="justify"&gt;
																	&lt;p&gt;
																		Amazing Pendant!!! My name is Aubrey Swee, I&amp;rsquo;m a FitnessFirst Personal Trainer and Group Exercise Instructor. I got to know this pendant from Jean Daniels. I like it because it has many benefits. I had a stiff neck due to an accident on 01st January 2007. I went on Parasailing with speedboat alone in Penang. I&amp;rsquo;d dropped into sea, being pulled in and out of the water by the speedboat. As a result, my wrist, elbow, left knee and the back of my neck were hurt. Subsequently, I&amp;rsquo;d visited the chiropractor and the physiotherapist a few times just to get rid of these soreness. However, the back of my neck still remains stiff. I&amp;rsquo;ve to do a lot of stretching just to keep it flexible and the soreness away. Miracle happened! Right after I started wearing the FusionExcel&amp;rsquo;s Quantum Pendant for 2 weeks, this sore neck of mine started to disappear and now the sore is completely gone. Also, whenever I&amp;rsquo;m doing my personal training or class, I could do more weights with the exercise machine. This Quantum Pendant really helps me a lot. Because of this, I started to share its amazing benefits with my clients and to help them to improve their flexibility, energy or strength level. Thanks to FusionExcel for the amazing Quantum Pendant.&lt;/p&gt;
																&lt;/div&gt;
															&lt;/td&gt;
														&lt;/tr&gt;
													&lt;/tbody&gt;
												&lt;/table&gt;
											&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="10" width="740"&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="267" valign="top"&gt;
				&lt;table background="img/testimonial_bg.jpg" bgcolor="#eef0fc" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" style="border:solid 1px #000000" width="100%"&gt;
					&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="25" valign="top" width="738"&gt;
								&lt;table background="img/buttonbg2.gif" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td class="header_title_white" height="25" width="738"&gt;
												&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;a id="rachel" name="rachel"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#ffffff; font-weight:bold;"&gt;Rachel Ngo, 32 Years Old, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="231" valign="top"&gt;
								&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td height="221" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
												&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
													&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
													&lt;tbody&gt;
														&lt;tr&gt;
															&lt;td class="content" height="221" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
																&lt;div align="justify"&gt;
																	In April 2006, I had a fall and fractured my left ankle. Due to this accident, I began to use my right leg more to move about. Not long after that I realized I began to suffer from severe pain on my right leg. I was unable to bend my knees. I used to dislike walking up and down the stairs. I had to walk up one step at a time.&lt;br /&gt;
																	&lt;br /&gt;
																	My situation got worse, I began to seek for doctor&amp;rsquo;s advice. I was prescribed a capsule that would help to reduce my knee pain. I had to consume 2 tablets daily. Even after consuming the prescribed medicine, I could still feel numbness on the knees and the pain persisted.&lt;br /&gt;
																	&lt;br /&gt;
																	One day I visited my friend. I shared with him my predicament. He immediately recommended me to try the Quantum Pendant. He tested the Quantum Pendant on me and I could immediately feel the effect in just 5 minutes. I felt there were some gushing types of movement in knees. And for the first time after so many months, I felt relieved.&lt;br /&gt;
																	&lt;br /&gt;
																	Straight away I ordered the Quantum Pendant. Now after wearing the pendant for 1 week, my knees are feeling very much better. I no longer dread walking the stairs anymore. For a matter of fact, I&amp;rsquo;m even able to run up the stairs. I don&amp;rsquo;t have anymore crackling sound while I walk. The uncomfortable pain on my knees has reduced substantially. Thank God for my friend who showed me the Quantum Pendant.&lt;br /&gt;
																	&lt;br /&gt;
																	Thank you FusionExcel for this marvellous product.&lt;/div&gt;
															&lt;/td&gt;
														&lt;/tr&gt;
													&lt;/tbody&gt;
												&lt;/table&gt;
											&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="10" width="740"&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="233" valign="top"&gt;
				&lt;table bgcolor="#eef0fc" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" style="border:solid 1px #000000" width="100%"&gt;
					&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="25" valign="top" width="738"&gt;
								&lt;table background="img/buttonbg2.gif" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td class="header_title_white" height="25" width="738"&gt;
												&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;a id="mali" name="mali"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#ffffff; font-weight:bold;"&gt; Mali, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="197" valign="top"&gt;
								&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td height="187" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
												&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
													&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
													&lt;tbody&gt;
														&lt;tr&gt;
															&lt;td class="content" height="187" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
																&lt;div align="justify"&gt;
																	I was 49 years old when it finally dawned on me that the reason for my frequent knee pain, whenever I climbed stairs or go driving, is not only sign of old age, but a serious knee problem. I subsequently went to the doctor who prescribed glucosomine. That has been great for my knee except that I don&amp;#39;t take it so often. I am not a great believer of taking western medication for fear of future side effect, especially on the kidney that was 5 years ago. So now, when my friend, Rena introduced me to Quantum Pendant, I signed up immediately, convinced that this is my miracle cure. I decided to stop taking the medication on the first day of wearing the pendant, just to test the effectiveness. Thank God, the pendant works for me and now, not only do I stopped the medication completely but also the pain is gone and driving long distance means continuous trip without having to do frequent stop. Thanks Rena for introducing me to FusionExcel&amp;#39;s Quantum Pendant and thanks FusionExcel for the wonderful product.&lt;/div&gt;
															&lt;/td&gt;
														&lt;/tr&gt;
													&lt;/tbody&gt;
												&lt;/table&gt;
											&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="10" width="740"&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="267" valign="top"&gt;
				&lt;table background="img/testimonial_bg.jpg" bgcolor="#eef0fc" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" style="border:solid 1px #000000" width="100%"&gt;
					&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="25" valign="top" width="738"&gt;
								&lt;table background="img/buttonbg2.gif" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td class="header_title_white" height="25" width="738"&gt;
												&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;a id="datinHjh" name="datinHjh"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#ffffff; font-weight:bold;"&gt; Datin Hjh Che Barni Bt Hj Mohd Noor, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="231" valign="top"&gt;
								&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td height="221" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
												&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
													&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
													&lt;tbody&gt;
														&lt;tr&gt;
															&lt;td class="content" height="221" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
																&lt;div align="justify"&gt;
																	I wish to share a personal experience about how the FusionExcel Quantum Pendant has helped to change my life.&lt;br /&gt;
																	&lt;br /&gt;
																	In July 2006, while holidaying in Langkawi, I was struck with an unidentifiable sickness. From being able to walk, I was suddenly bedridden overnight. The pain was so excruciating that I cried every time I move even a tiny bit. I was transferred by ambulance to Alor Setar General Hospital and was hospitalized for two weeks. From the MRI they discovered there were damages to my Lumber 3, 4 and 5 and as well as to my Sacrum 1.&lt;br /&gt;
																	&lt;br /&gt;
																	Many doctors advised me to accept the worst, that I will be confined to a wheelchair. I refuse to accept that fate and began my therapy for about three months. Even then I still can&amp;#39;t walk more than five steps without having to grasp hold onto something for support. I cried with every walk because of the severe pain. Since the disease also affected my nervous system, my left leg could not function normally. My left leg get confusing signals that at times it felt pricking pains or numbness and at other times it gets severe pain. I could not sleep at night because my whole body was in pain.&lt;br /&gt;
																	&lt;br /&gt;
																	I met someone in Kuala Lumpur selling the FusionExcel Quantum Pendant. I was skeptical about the pendant initially but I have nothing to lose but to try anything. Strangely enough, as if it is a miracle, after continuously wearing the Quantum Pendant, the pain begins to subside especially on my left leg. I am able to get good night sleep again, something that I was deprived of for several months.&lt;br /&gt;
																	&lt;br /&gt;
																	Now I am so thankful that I am able to get back my normal life again. Some of the doctors are even amazed &amp;amp; curious at my speedy recovery. My blood pressure is normal again and I feel energetic. I go to office as usual and do not feel anymore pain in my leg especially when the air conditioner is on compare to the pain I get when the room is cold without wearing the Quantum Pendant. I believe the Quantum Pendant has contributed &amp;amp; assisted me much to get my Normal Life back again.
																	&lt;p&gt;
																		&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
																	&lt;br /&gt;
																	&lt;br /&gt;
																	Thank you FusionExcel for the amazing Life Changing &amp;amp; Saving product!&lt;/div&gt;
															&lt;/td&gt;
														&lt;/tr&gt;
													&lt;/tbody&gt;
												&lt;/table&gt;
											&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="10" width="740"&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="267" valign="top"&gt;
				&lt;table background="img/testimonial_bg.jpg" bgcolor="#eef0fc" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" style="border:solid 1px #000000" width="100%"&gt;
					&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="25" valign="top" width="738"&gt;
								&lt;table background="img/buttonbg2.gif" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td class="header_title_white" height="25" width="738"&gt;
												&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;a id="joyce" name="joyce"&gt; &lt;span style="color:#ffffff; font-weight:bold;"&gt;Joyce, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia, 45 Years Old. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="231" valign="top"&gt;
								&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td height="221" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
												&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
													&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
													&lt;tbody&gt;
														&lt;tr&gt;
															&lt;td class="content" height="221" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
																&lt;div align="justify"&gt;
																	&lt;p&gt;
																		When I was first introduced to the FusionExcel&amp;rsquo;s Quantum Pendant by my colleague, I was rather doubtful about the product. However, with several simple demonstrations, it impressed a lot. I decided to buy one for myself. As I brought it home, I wore it on myself and I used it to energize the drinking water. My family thought it was a crazy act to spend such amount for the Quantum Pendant. They suggested I should buy gold pendant instead! What a coincidence, my 10 years old son complaint of ear pain. I brought him to see doctor and he still complained about the pain after medication. He even cried whenever the ear medication prescribed by doctor was applied to his ear.&lt;br /&gt;
																		&lt;br /&gt;
																		I decided to put on the Quantum Pendant around his neck and let him drink the energized water. On the following day, he told me that the ear pain has already disappeared. However, since it helped him to get rid the pain he kept on wearing it. Two days later he accidentally hit the Quantum Pendant to the basin. It cracked and broke into few pieces. The Quantum Pendant was glued back by my spouse without my knowledge. Before I went off for Chinese New Year holidays, I simply put the Quantum Pendant under my &amp;ldquo;Lokam&amp;rdquo; (mandarin oranges) on display at the living room. What a surprise I found that the &amp;ldquo;Lokam&amp;rdquo; still looks fresh and juicy even after one week. I compared the &amp;ldquo;charged&amp;rdquo; mandarin oranges with some other mandarin oranges from the fridge. The mandarin oranges in the fridge look like old lady skin and dry compared with those mandarin oranges displayed at the living room that was charged by the Quantum Pendant. Additionally I even compared them to the small pineapple on display at the living room that normally would last longer. However unlike the &amp;ldquo;charged&amp;rdquo; mandarin oranges, the small pineapple looks very dry and rotten too.&lt;br /&gt;
																		&lt;br /&gt;
																		The Quantum Pendant is truly an amazing product. Although it already broke (and glued back) I still treasure it.&lt;/p&gt;
																&lt;/div&gt;
															&lt;/td&gt;
														&lt;/tr&gt;
													&lt;/tbody&gt;
												&lt;/table&gt;
											&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="10" width="740"&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="199" valign="top"&gt;
				&lt;table bgcolor="#eef0fc" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" style="border:solid 1px #000000" width="100%"&gt;
					&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="25" valign="top" width="738"&gt;
								&lt;table background="img/buttonbg2.gif" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td class="header_title_white" height="25" width="738"&gt;
												&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;a id="suraya" name="suraya"&gt; &lt;span style="color:#ffffff; font-weight:bold;"&gt;Suraya Hj. Abdul Rani, 46 years old, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="163" valign="top"&gt;
								&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td height="153" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
												&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
													&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
													&lt;tbody&gt;
														&lt;tr&gt;
															&lt;td class="content" height="153" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
																&lt;div align="justify"&gt;
																	Due to a road accident, I have had arthritis in my right knee for the past 22 years. Lately, for the past 6 years, my knee has gotten worse asI have had to manage my two physically handicapped boys aged 19 and 22 on my own daily. To make matters worse, I stopped taking the pain killers that were making me put on weight continuously. I couldn&amp;#39;t shake off the weight until I started taking FusionExcel&amp;#39;s Fat Loss Program. However last week, another miracle happened. I decided to try the Quantum Pendant, just for the fun of it. Guess what, that same night, all the pain in my knee which I had for 22 years disappeared. Not only that, I could turn both my knees any way I want and I could get up and walk immediately without pain, something I couldn&amp;#39;t do before. You should try it, using is believing!&lt;/div&gt;
															&lt;/td&gt;
														&lt;/tr&gt;
													&lt;/tbody&gt;
												&lt;/table&gt;
											&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="10" width="740"&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="80" valign="top"&gt;
				&lt;table bgcolor="#eef0fc" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" style="border:solid 1px #000000" width="100%"&gt;
					&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="25" valign="top" width="738"&gt;
								&lt;table background="img/buttonbg2.gif" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td class="header_title_white" height="25" width="738"&gt;
												&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a id="madamTan" name="madamTan"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#ffffff; font-weight:bold;"&gt; Madam Tan.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="44" valign="top"&gt;
								&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td height="34" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
												&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
													&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
													&lt;tbody&gt;
														&lt;tr&gt;
															&lt;td class="content" height="34" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
																&lt;div align="justify"&gt;
																	My 72 yrs old mother suffered a stroke. During the 2 weeks after the stroke she was always in the state of semi-consciousness &amp;amp; sleeping most of the time. My friend asked me to try FusionExcel International&amp;rsquo;s Quantum Pendant on her to see if it could bring any help to her. After only putting on FusionExcel International&amp;rsquo;s Quantum Pendant for just few hours, I was amazed to see her able to sit up on her own &amp;amp; being in a more conscious state. I am truly excited about this amazing product. Thank you FusionExcel for such an amazing product!&lt;/div&gt;
															&lt;/td&gt;
														&lt;/tr&gt;
													&lt;/tbody&gt;
												&lt;/table&gt;
											&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="10" width="740"&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="80" valign="top"&gt;
				&lt;table bgcolor="#eef0fc" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" style="border:solid 1px #000000" width="100%"&gt;
					&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="25" valign="top" width="738"&gt;
								&lt;table background="img/buttonbg2.gif" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td class="header_title_white" height="25" width="738"&gt;
												&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a id="leeLH" name="leeLH"&gt; &lt;span style="color:#ffffff; font-weight:bold;"&gt;Mr. Lee LH. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="44" valign="top"&gt;
								&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td height="34" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
												&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
													&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
													&lt;tbody&gt;
														&lt;tr&gt;
															&lt;td class="content" height="34" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
																&lt;div align="justify"&gt;
																	I suffered a few crushed ribs from a vehicle accident I met with last year. I was not able to lift my arms as a result of the crushed ribs. My friend brought the FusionExcel International&amp;rsquo;s Quantum Pendant to let me try. After putting on the Quantum Pendant for less than an hour, a miracle happened! I was not only able to move &amp;amp; lift my arms easily, I could even swing my arms! I could hardly believe it myself! It&amp;rsquo;s a miraculous product! I immediately bought some to give to my family members too. I also recommend it to all my friends. Thank you FusionExcel.&lt;/div&gt;
															&lt;/td&gt;
														&lt;/tr&gt;
													&lt;/tbody&gt;
												&lt;/table&gt;
											&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="10" width="740"&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="80" valign="top"&gt;
				&lt;table background="img/testimonial_bg.jpg" bgcolor="#eef0fc" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" style="border:solid 1px #000000" width="100%"&gt;
					&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="25" valign="top" width="738"&gt;
								&lt;table background="img/buttonbg2.gif" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td class="header_title_white" height="25" width="738"&gt;
												&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a id="nirmala" name="nirmala"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#ffffff; font-weight:bold;"&gt; Nirmala, Klang, Malaysia, 27 Years Old. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="44" valign="top"&gt;
								&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td height="34" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
												&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
													&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
													&lt;tbody&gt;
														&lt;tr&gt;
															&lt;td class="content" height="34" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
																&lt;div align="justify"&gt;
																	&lt;p&gt;
																		On Thursday evening (05th October 2006) I returned home from work to find my mother lying on the sofa looking very tired. Being concerned I immediately ask her what has happened to her because I fear that she might have another relapse of heart attack. She complained to me that her whole body was aching and was having high fever. Immediately I decided to let her put on the Quantum Pendant. Subsequently I went about doing my chores. About half an hour later I came back to check on her condition. However I found her missing from the sofa. I panic and look everywhere not knowing what has happened to her. To my surprised I saw her standing at the gate. She looked much better &amp;amp; was more cheerful. She told me that the high fever has amazingly subsided &amp;amp; also that she felt more energetic to walk around. I am truly happy that the Quantum Pendant is able to bring instantaneous healing to my mother in just a matter of 30 minutes!&lt;br /&gt;
																		&lt;br /&gt;
																		On Sunday (08th October 2006), my father took me to visit one of his friends who was suffering with pain all over his body. After putting on the Quantum Pendant for about half an hour, he told us that he could feel very much relieved from his body aches. Prior to our visit, he could not even lift up his right arm on itself without the help of his left hand raising it. However after wearing the Quantum Pendant for 30min he was not only able to miraculously lift his right arm on its own, he could even swing it around on its own and without pain! Thank you FusionExcel for such a wonderful product!&lt;/p&gt;
																&lt;/div&gt;
															&lt;/td&gt;
														&lt;/tr&gt;
													&lt;/tbody&gt;
												&lt;/table&gt;
											&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="10" width="740"&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="80" valign="top"&gt;
				&lt;table background="img/testimonial_bg.jpg" bgcolor="#eef0fc" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" style="border:solid 1px #000000" width="100%"&gt;
					&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="25" valign="top" width="738"&gt;
								&lt;table background="img/buttonbg2.gif" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td class="header_title_white" height="25" width="738"&gt;
												&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;a id="WongKH" name="WongKH"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#ffffff; font-weight:bold;"&gt; Mr. Wong KH.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="44" valign="top"&gt;
								&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td height="34" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
												&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
													&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
													&lt;tbody&gt;
														&lt;tr&gt;
															&lt;td class="content" height="34" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
																&lt;div align="justify"&gt;
																	&lt;p&gt;
																		My 63 years old father had an accidental fall in November last year. As a result his neck was affected &amp;amp; was weak. For the past two months, his head was stoop down most of the time &amp;amp; he was not able to utter much word or speak long sentences. My nephew introduced the FusionExcel International&amp;rsquo;s Quantum Pendant to me. I was skeptical about its healing powers initially. But anything that could possibly help to improve my father&amp;rsquo;s condition without putting him in any risk or danger is always worth a try. After all there was nothing to loose by trying. After putting on the FusionExcel International&amp;rsquo;s Quantum Pendant on my father for about 2 hours, he was able to lift up his head normally again! Not only that, he even spoke to me continuously for 2 amazing hours! I am so happy that my father&amp;rsquo;s condition is improving as a result of the Quantum Pendant. I immediately ordered the Quantum Pendants to give them to my family members too. Thank you FusionExcel for the incredible Quantum Pendant!&lt;/p&gt;
																&lt;/div&gt;
															&lt;/td&gt;
														&lt;/tr&gt;
													&lt;/tbody&gt;
												&lt;/table&gt;
											&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="10" width="740"&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="80" valign="top"&gt;
				&lt;table background="img/testimonial_bg.jpg" bgcolor="#eef0fc" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" style="border:solid 1px #000000" width="100%"&gt;
					&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="25" valign="top" width="738"&gt;
								&lt;table background="img/buttonbg2.gif" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td class="header_title_white" height="25" width="738"&gt;
												&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;a id="maramah" name="maramah"&gt; &lt;span style="color:#ffffff; font-weight:bold;"&gt;Maramah, Klang, Malaysia, 34 Years Old. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="44" valign="top"&gt;
								&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td height="34" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
												&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
													&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
													&lt;tbody&gt;
														&lt;tr&gt;
															&lt;td class="content" height="34" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
																&lt;div align="justify"&gt;
																	&lt;p&gt;
																		The Quantum Pendant gave me much relief from the nerve pain on my foot, which I had for more than 3 years. I had to wear flat shoes. After only wearing for 2 hours, I experienced much relief. Now, I can finally wear the high heels again. Not only that, I can also walk longer distances without the nerve pain. I feel more energetic. Even though I sleep late, when I get up, I don&amp;rsquo;t feel any giddiness, and I am not tired at all.&lt;br /&gt;
																		&lt;br /&gt;
																		A friend of mine has an 8 years old son, who was admitted to the hospital. She told me that her son doesn&amp;rsquo;t have any appetite and did not take any foods or even a drop of milk that day. She invited us to try the Quantum Pendant on her son to see if it could help him. Initially I was quite hesitant, since the patient was a young child. But the mother was quite insistent, so my friends and myself visited the boy at the hospital. We let the boy wear the pendant for 20 minutes. Subsequently, we let him drink the water which was energized by the Quantum Pendant. Within 10 minutes, the boy could sit up on his own. Subsequently, we left the hospital. Just 10 minutes later, the mother called me to inform that her son has asked for rice to eat. We were all thrilled at the amazing result of the Quantum Pendant even on a young child.&lt;br /&gt;
																		&lt;br /&gt;
																		In another case, there&amp;rsquo;s an elderly lady who was bed-ridden for 4 years. Likewise, we did not dare to try the Quantum Pendant on her, but due to a friend&amp;rsquo;s insistence, again we went to try the Quantum Pendant on her. We energized the water using the Quantum Pendant over her neck. Her daughter told us that normally her mother could not sit up more than 15 minutes at any one time. That night, after drinking the energized water and wearing the Quantum Pendant, she could sit up for 45 minutes.&lt;br /&gt;
																		&lt;br /&gt;
																		The Quantum Pendant is truly an amazing product. It has now become my soul mate!&lt;/p&gt;
																&lt;/div&gt;
															&lt;/td&gt;
														&lt;/tr&gt;
													&lt;/tbody&gt;
												&lt;/table&gt;
											&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="10" width="740"&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="80" valign="top"&gt;
				&lt;table bgcolor="#eef0fc" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" style="border:solid 1px #000000" width="100%"&gt;
					&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="25" valign="top" width="738"&gt;
								&lt;table background="img/buttonbg2.gif" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td class="header_title_white" height="25" width="738"&gt;
												&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;a id="AlicePhua" name="AlicePhua"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#ffffff; font-weight:bold;"&gt; Alice Phua, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia, 38 Years Old. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="44" valign="top"&gt;
								&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td height="34" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
												&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
													&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
													&lt;tbody&gt;
														&lt;tr&gt;
															&lt;td class="content" height="34" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
																&lt;div align="justify"&gt;
																	When I wear the Quantum Pendant, I feel not so tired at the end of a hectic working day. I can also walk up t or 3 flights of stairs without feeling short of breath. Also, while I was having a sore throat, I placed the Quantum Pendant on my throat and I feel the relief of less pain. Thank you, FusionExcel, for a wonderful product!&lt;/div&gt;
															&lt;/td&gt;
														&lt;/tr&gt;
													&lt;/tbody&gt;
												&lt;/table&gt;
											&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="10" width="740"&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="80" valign="top"&gt;
				&lt;table bgcolor="#eef0fc" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" style="border:solid 1px #000000" width="100%"&gt;
					&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="25" valign="top" width="738"&gt;
								&lt;table background="img/buttonbg2.gif" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td class="header_title_white" height="25" width="738"&gt;
												&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a id="intanSofia" name="intanSofia"&gt; &lt;span style="color:#ffffff; font-weight:bold;"&gt;Intan Sofia, Selayang, Malaysia, 41 Years Old. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="44" valign="top"&gt;
								&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td height="34" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
												&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
													&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
													&lt;tbody&gt;
														&lt;tr&gt;
															&lt;td class="content" height="34" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
																&lt;div align="justify"&gt;
																	I am one of the temporary beauticians in FusionExcel. I have to treat a lot of customers daily. Sometimes, up to a hundred or more. Frankly, I usually feel tired but always try to give the best service to all. Fortunately, few days back, FusionExcel gave me the chance to put on the Quantum Pendant. It was tremendously good. I didn&amp;rsquo;t feel tired like before. I felt more energetic instead. I am still wearing it now. The number of customers is no longer a big issue for me, in fact, the more the better.&lt;/div&gt;
															&lt;/td&gt;
														&lt;/tr&gt;
													&lt;/tbody&gt;
												&lt;/table&gt;
											&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="10" width="740"&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="80" valign="top"&gt;
				&lt;table bgcolor="#eef0fc" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" style="border:solid 1px #000000" width="100%"&gt;
					&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="25" valign="top" width="738"&gt;
								&lt;table background="img/buttonbg2.gif" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td class="header_title_white" height="25" width="738"&gt;
												&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;a id="thtan" name="thtan"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#ffffff; font-weight:bold;"&gt;T.H.TAN, Petaling Jaya, Malaysia, 46 Years Old. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="44" valign="top"&gt;
								&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td height="34" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
												&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
													&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
													&lt;tbody&gt;
														&lt;tr&gt;
															&lt;td class="content" height="34" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
																&lt;div align="justify"&gt;
																	I used to be breathless when I climb the 5 flights of stairs to my office. When I started wearing FusionExcel&amp;rsquo;s Quantum Pendant, I was amazed that I can now climb the same 5 flights of stairs Without becoming breathless! Now I am full of energy all day long and I can also focus more sharply on my work. My overall endurance has improved. Thank you so much, FusionExcel, for your amazing Quantum Pendant!&lt;/div&gt;
															&lt;/td&gt;
														&lt;/tr&gt;
													&lt;/tbody&gt;
												&lt;/table&gt;
											&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="10" width="740"&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="80" valign="top"&gt;
				&lt;table bgcolor="#eef0fc" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" style="border:solid 1px #000000" width="100%"&gt;
					&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="25" valign="top" width="738"&gt;
								&lt;table background="img/buttonbg2.gif" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td class="header_title_white" height="25" width="738"&gt;
												&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;a id="Sherry" name="Sherry"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#ffffff; font-weight:bold;"&gt;Sherry Leong, Penang, Malaysia, 46 Years Old. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="44" valign="top"&gt;
								&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td height="34" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
												&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
													&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
													&lt;tbody&gt;
														&lt;tr&gt;
															&lt;td class="content" height="34" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
																&lt;div align="justify"&gt;
																	Firstly, I would like to thank FusionExcel for introducing me to this wonderful product (Quantum Pendant). Previously, I would be quite tired after a whole days work, and experienced migraines on and off. But after a few days of wearing the Quantum Pendant, I felt very energetic and my mind felt very focused and relaxed. All fellow members of FusionExcel, please get yourself one or you will regret it, because it really does improve our health condition.&lt;/div&gt;
															&lt;/td&gt;
														&lt;/tr&gt;
													&lt;/tbody&gt;
												&lt;/table&gt;
											&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="10" width="740"&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="80" valign="top"&gt;
				&lt;table bgcolor="#eef0fc" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" style="border:solid 1px #000000" width="100%"&gt;
					&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="25" valign="top" width="738"&gt;
								&lt;table background="img/buttonbg2.gif" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td class="header_title_white" height="25" width="738"&gt;
												&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;a id="ChengYee" name="ChengYee"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#ffffff; font-weight:bold;"&gt; Chan Cheng Yee, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia, 42 Years old.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="44" valign="top"&gt;
								&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td height="34" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
												&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
													&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
													&lt;tbody&gt;
														&lt;tr&gt;
															&lt;td class="content" height="34" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
																&lt;div align="justify"&gt;
																	I am simply impressed with FusionExcel&amp;rsquo;s new Quantum Pendant. When I put on the Quantum Pendant, I feel energetic and can work on the PC up till early morning (3am) without even feeling tired, which I normally do without the Quantum Pendant. I introduced the Quantum Pendant to my friend who had spinal back ache and just amazingly within 20 minutes, she could feel the relief. My cousin who also bought the Quantum Pendant told me that after wearing it her ankle pain has subsided substantially. Thank you, FusionExcel, for another wonderful product.&lt;/div&gt;
															&lt;/td&gt;
														&lt;/tr&gt;
													&lt;/tbody&gt;
												&lt;/table&gt;
											&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="10" width="740"&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="80" valign="top"&gt;
				&lt;table background="img/testimonial_bg.jpg" bgcolor="#eef0fc" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" style="border:solid 1px #000000" width="100%"&gt;
					&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="25" valign="top" width="738"&gt;
								&lt;table background="img/buttonbg2.gif" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td class="header_title_white" height="25" width="738"&gt;
												&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;a id="JohnChang" name="JohnChang"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#ffffff; font-weight:bold;"&gt;John Chang, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia, 38 Years Old.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="44" valign="top"&gt;
								&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td height="34" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
												&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
													&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
													&lt;tbody&gt;
														&lt;tr&gt;
															&lt;td class="content" height="34" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
																&lt;div align="justify"&gt;
																	I used to consume energy drinks like Livita and Redbull as well as B-Complex supplements daily because I usually felt tired by the end of the day. After putting on the Quantum Pendant, I don&amp;rsquo;t feel tired even past midnight. There is a sustained constant supply of energy to the body. I used to spend more than RM 200 each month on energy drink and supplements. Now, it is a RM 2,400 yearly savings for me!! I was told that the Quantum Pendant can supply the energy incredibly forever! Wow, that&amp;rsquo;s super savings! Thank you, FusionExcel for another fantastic product.&lt;br /&gt;
																	&lt;br /&gt;
																	I believe this product will help a lot of people who need to re-energize themselves now and then especially those working long office hours or double shifts, taxi, bus and lorry drivers, security guards, construction workers, or who partake in activities like mountain hiking, climbing, cycling, jogging and other exercise and sport. With the Deepavali &amp;amp; Hari Raya coming, many will &amp;ldquo;Balik Kampung&amp;rdquo;. The Quantum Pendant would help many drivers balik kampung without feeling tired and more alert during the long hours of driving and more importantly it will means safety for their own family members &amp;amp; passengers in the car as well as other cars too by not knocking into them due to tiredness.&lt;/div&gt;
															&lt;/td&gt;
														&lt;/tr&gt;
													&lt;/tbody&gt;
												&lt;/table&gt;
											&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="10" width="740"&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="80" valign="top"&gt;
				&lt;table bgcolor="#eef0fc" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" style="border:solid 1px #000000" width="100%"&gt;
					&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="25" valign="top" width="738"&gt;
								&lt;table background="img/buttonbg2.gif" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td class="header_title_white" height="25" width="738"&gt;
												&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;a id="siti" name="siti"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#ffffff; font-weight:bold;"&gt;Siti Khadijah Abu Hassan, Cheras, 33 Years Old. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="44" valign="top"&gt;
								&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td height="34" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
												&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
													&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
													&lt;tbody&gt;
														&lt;tr&gt;
															&lt;td class="content" height="34" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
																&lt;div align="justify"&gt;
																	I am a 90 kg lady who still likes to wear high heels while doing my work as a temporary beautician in FusionExcel. I guess you guys out there can imagine how difficult it is for me to carry my own weight running here and there to treat and service customers, washing necessary items, changing bedsheets, towels and a lot more, especially now, which is the fasting month, without food I feel as if my energy is all gone. However, thanks to FusionExcel for lending me the Quantum Pendant to rectify the problem. I am feeling much more energetic and active after wearing it, it was as if my weight is just 50 kg! Now, I don&amp;rsquo;t easily feel hungry and tired so fast like last time. I feel good!&lt;/div&gt;
															&lt;/td&gt;
														&lt;/tr&gt;
													&lt;/tbody&gt;
												&lt;/table&gt;
											&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="10" width="740"&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="80" valign="top"&gt;
				&lt;table bgcolor="#eef0fc" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" style="border:solid 1px #000000" width="100%"&gt;
					&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="25" valign="top" width="738"&gt;
								&lt;table background="img/buttonbg2.gif" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td class="header_title_white" height="25" width="738"&gt;
												&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a id="fairus" name="fairus"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#ffffff; font-weight:bold;"&gt; Fairus Salleh, Pantai Dalam, 23 Years Old. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="44" valign="top"&gt;
								&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td height="34" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
												&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
													&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
													&lt;tbody&gt;
														&lt;tr&gt;
															&lt;td class="content" height="34" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
																&lt;div align="justify"&gt;
																	I am one of the workers of FusionExcel. Everyday I handle stocks. One day, FusionExcel loan me a pendant to wear. Since this pendant is believed can give more energy, I too wanted to try it. Honestly, I feel more energetic after using this &amp;ldquo;miracle&amp;rdquo; pendant. If last time I can only carry 3 boxes in one time, but by using this pendant now, I can carry 4 boxes. Plus, I feel less exhausted. You could not feel it without trying it. Seriously, this pendant is really superb.&lt;/div&gt;
															&lt;/td&gt;
														&lt;/tr&gt;
													&lt;/tbody&gt;
												&lt;/table&gt;
											&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="10" width="740"&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="80" valign="top"&gt;
				&lt;table background="img/testimonial_bg.jpg" bgcolor="#eef0fc" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" style="border:solid 1px #000000" width="100%"&gt;
					&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="25" valign="top" width="738"&gt;
								&lt;table background="img/buttonbg2.gif" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td class="header_title_white" height="25" width="738"&gt;
												&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;a id="davidPhua" name="davidPhua"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#ffffff; font-weight:bold;"&gt;David Phua, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia, 43 Years Old.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td height="44" valign="top"&gt;
								&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="10" width="100%"&gt;
									&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td height="34" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
												&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
													&lt;!--DWLayoutTable--&gt;
													&lt;tbody&gt;
														&lt;tr&gt;
															&lt;td class="content" height="34" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
																I want to thank the company FusionExcel for bringing such a wonderful product, Quantum Pendant. The benefits I got from:&lt;br /&gt;
																&lt;br /&gt;
																1) Wearing the Quantum Pendant, I feel:&lt;br /&gt;
																&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- less tired&lt;br /&gt;
																&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- more focused&lt;br /&gt;
																&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- better endurance while on a job&lt;br /&gt;
																&lt;br /&gt;
																2) Drinking the water charged by the Quantum Pendant:&lt;br /&gt;
																&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- the pain that I have on my right arm when I lift a heavy load is less painful.&lt;br /&gt;
																&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- feel less sleepy&lt;br /&gt;
																&lt;br /&gt;
																Thank You. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
														&lt;/tr&gt;
													&lt;/tbody&gt;
												&lt;/table&gt;
											&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content><meta><description>This is the first time our AHOO! Group organized a Dinner Event in Seremban on 25th June 2009 and the response was tremendous. A total of 320 participants gathered at Dragon Palace Restaurant, Oakland Commercial Centre and sat down to a sumptuous 9 course dinner.</description><keyword></keyword><robots>all</robots><author>klhunter</author></meta></en><bm><title>FusionExcel Event in Seremban 25th June 2009.</title><content></content><meta><description>This is the first time our AHOO! Group organized a Dinner Event in Seremban on 25th June 2009 and the response was tremendous. A total of 320 participants gathered at Dragon Palace Restaurant, Oakland Commercial Centre and sat down to a sumptuous 9 course dinner.</description><keyword></keyword><robots>all</robots><author>klhunter</author></meta></bm><chi><title>FusionExcel Event in Seremban 25th June 2009.</title><content></content><meta><description>This is the first time our AHOO! Group organized a Dinner Event in Seremban on 25th June 2009 and the response was tremendous. A total of 320 participants gathered at Dragon Palace Restaurant, Oakland Commercial Centre and sat down to a sumptuous 9 course dinner.</description><keyword></keyword><robots>all</robots><author>klhunter</author></meta></chi></article>
