<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?><article><en><title>Official Appointment</title><content>&lt;p&gt;
	&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table border=&quot;0&quot; cellpadding=&quot;0&quot; cellspacing=&quot;0&quot; style=&quot;color: rgb(0, 0, 0); font-family: Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 13px; text-align: justify; background-color: rgb(238, 240, 252); &quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr valign=&quot;top&quot;&gt;
			&lt;td align=&quot;center&quot; height=&quot;10&quot;&gt;
				&lt;div align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;
					&lt;span class=&quot;content&quot; style=&quot;text-align: justify; &quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FusionExcel Welcomes Former Miss Malaysia, Maggie Loo, as Ambassador for &amp;quot;Hope For Children&amp;quot; Charity Initiative!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr valign=&quot;top&quot;&gt;
			&lt;td align=&quot;center&quot; height=&quot;10&quot;&gt;
				&lt;img height=&quot;299&quot; src=&quot;http://www.fusionexcel.com/imgnews/corporate_spokesman_maggieloo_1.jpg&quot; width=&quot;448&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr valign=&quot;top&quot;&gt;
			&lt;td class=&quot;content&quot; height=&quot;10&quot;&gt;
				FusionExcel is proud to announce the appointment of former Miss Malaysia, Maggie Loo, as FE&amp;#39;s Ambassador for FE&amp;#39;s &amp;quot;Hope For Children&amp;quot; Charity initiative, a charity campaign to help the less fortunate and needy children of this world.&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;br /&gt;
				Maggie is renowned in the world of beauty, fashion, grooming and modeling. Maggie started her modeling career in the early seventies. In 1973 she won the prestigious Miss Malaysia crown and represented Malaysia in Athens, Greece. She also represented Malaysia in the Miss World Tourism in Japan and graced many international events as ambassadress for Malaysia.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;br /&gt;
				Upon returning to Malaysia, she opened her own modeling academy where she has trained countless young talents, both males and females, to become successful models and household names like herself.&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;br /&gt;
				Maggie was the first to introduce the luncheon and tea fashion shows to the Malaysian public and also pioneered modeling and grooming courses, setting the pace and standard for the country in this area.&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;br /&gt;
				Dubbed the &amp;quot;Queen Maker&amp;quot;, the &amp;quot;Talent Spotter&amp;quot; by the press, Maggie personally trained many of her students to become Malaysia&amp;#39;s ambassadors and winners of many beauty pageants and competitions. She is proud to say she has trained, groomed and produced more than a dozen Miss Malaysians and well known celebrities like Datuk Yasmin Yusuf, Datuk Anna Lim, Nancie Foo, Christina Mary Lim, Siti Rohani, Anne Looi, Irene Wong, Puspa Salleh, Datuk Shah Rezza, Elaine Kang, etc.&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;br /&gt;
				In 1987, she met Madame Eileen Ford, the head of the world renowned Ford Models Incorporated, New York, who granted her the franchise for the Super Model of the World Pageant for Malaysia.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
</content><meta><description>Maggie Loo as FusionExcel Spokesperson for our amazing Quantum Pendant.</description><keyword>Miss Malaysia, Quantum Pendant</keyword><robots>all</robots><author>klhunter</author></meta></en><bm><title>Official Appointment</title><content></content><meta><description>Maggie Loo as FusionExcel Spokesperson for our amazing Quantum Pendant.</description><keyword>Miss Malaysia, Quantum Pendant</keyword><robots>all</robots><author>klhunter</author></meta></bm><chi><title>Official Appointment</title><content></content><meta><description>Maggie Loo as FusionExcel Spokesperson for our amazing Quantum Pendant.</description><keyword>Miss Malaysia, Quantum Pendant</keyword><robots>all</robots><author>klhunter</author></meta></chi></article>