<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<article>
	<en>
		<title>FE Welcomes Spokesman, Master Bahauddin Yap. </title>
		<alt_title></alt_title>
		<content>&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td valign="top" width="30%"&gt;
				&lt;img height="266" src="http://fusionexcel.com/imgnews/partner_master.jpg" width="200" /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
			&lt;td class="content" style="font-family: Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 13px; color: rgb(0, 0, 0); text-align: justify; " valign="top" width="70%"&gt;
				Master Bahauddin Richard Yap has spent most of his teenage years in search for esoteric knowledge and has since graduated from various spiritual/ mystery schools. He is now the founding member of his own esoteric / mystery school: Integrated Studies of Inner Science, or better known as ISIS. He has since trained more than a thousand Reiki practitioners, 117 Reiki Masters and more than a dozen clairvoyants.&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;br /&gt;
				Having graduated and trained by various Grand Masters and Masters of Energy Works, he is now actively promoting his own teaching which are also the synthesize teachings of his Masters. After 15 years of research and experiments, he founded eFusion Natural Healing System in 2006, a form of healing art derived from a combination of various healing modalities. With his remarkable knowledge in energy works, he is being regarded as the Master of Psychic Self Defense by his teachers and peers. He has since developed a new powerful extension art of Psychic Self Defense called applied Psychic Self Defense.&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;br /&gt;
				He is a Professional and Clinical Hypnotherapist. A member of International Association of Counselors and Therapist (IACT), an associate member of British Society of Clinical Hypnosis (BSCH) and one of the founding member of BSCH-Asia Chapter. Being a pioneer in Hypno Reiki in his birth country Malaysia, he has successfully treated countless patients using this method.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;br /&gt;
				Master Yap has trained countless people on energy product on the knowledge and usage of energies to human beings. He is instrumental in imparting the understanding of how energy works and the inter-relation of energies and one&amp;#39;s physical body.&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</content>
		<meta>
			<description></description>
			<keyword></keyword>
			<author>KLHunter</author>
			<robots>all</robots>
		</meta>
	</en>
	<bm>
		<title>FE Welcomes Spokesman, Master Bahauddin Yap. </title>
		<alt_title></alt_title>
		<content></content>
		<meta>
			<description></description>
			<keyword></keyword>
			<author>KLHunter</author>
			<robots>all</robots>
		</meta>
	</bm>
	<chi>
		<title>FE Welcomes Spokesman, Master Bahauddin Yap. </title>
		<alt_title></alt_title>
		<content></content>
		<meta>
			<description></description>
			<keyword></keyword>
			<author>KLHunter</author>
			<robots>all</robots>
		</meta>
	</chi>
</article>
