<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<article><en><title>Fusion Excel's Medical Consultant And Speaker: Dr. Amir Farid Isahak.</title><content>&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" style="color: rgb(0, 0, 0); font-family: 'Times New Roman'; background-color: rgb(238, 240, 252); font-size: medium; " width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td valign="top"&gt;
				&lt;img height="204" src="http://www.fusionexcel.com/imgnews/medicalconsultant.jpg" width="158" /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td valign="top"&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td class="content" style="font-family: Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 13px; text-align: justify; " valign="top"&gt;
				&lt;strong&gt;DR AMIR FARID ISAHAK&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;[ MBBS (Qld,Aust), MMED (Spore), MRCOG (UK) ] is a senior medical consultant/gynecologist with nearly 30 years of practicing. In Malaysia, he is one of the pioneers practising Anti-Aging Medicine and Holistic Integrated Medicine (combining modern, natural and complementary therapies); and in promoting Natural HRT for Menopause in Malaysian women. In the last 5 years he has turned his expertise to Medical Aesthetics, Medical Slimming therapies and Aesthetic Surgery. He is also certified in Stem Cell Therapy and Laser Slimming Therapy.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;br /&gt;
				Although trained in Modern Medicine (practicing Obstetrics/Gynecology, Family Practice, Anti-Aging and Aesthetic Medicine), he is a firm believer and practitioner of Holistic Health, Alternative/Complementary Therapies, Energy Medicine, Integrated Medicine, Predictive and Preventive Medicine, Energy, Nutritional Healing and Spiritual Healing.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;br /&gt;
				He was the Founding President of Guolin Qigong Association Malaysia and was also the Vice-President of the Malaysian Reiki Association. He has been practising and teaching Qigong (Islamic, Guolin, Xiangong and Shaolin Qigong) nearly 20 years, and is a respected Qigong Master and Reiki Master.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;br /&gt;
				He is also trained in Healing Tao, Hypnosis, Islamic Unani Medicine, Mind Science, Pranic Healing, Phytobiophysics, Psychic Healing, Silva Mind Control, Sufi Healing, and Kundalini Yoga.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;br /&gt;
				His areas of special interest include &amp;ndash; Antioxidants &amp;amp; Free Radicals ; BioEnergetic Healing, Cancer Therapy; Cell/Placenta&amp;nbsp; Therapies;&amp;nbsp; Detoxification; Enzymes; Functional Foods; Raw Foods; Mind-Body Medicine; Oxygen and Ozone Therapies; and&amp;nbsp; Probiotics.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;br /&gt;
				He is a popular health columnist for The Star newspaper, writing on Qigong, Wellness, Nutrition and other Health topics. His &amp;ldquo;Art of Qi/Art of Healing&amp;rdquo; health column has been published fortnightly for over 5 years.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</content><meta><description>As a football striker FusionExcel's Quantum Pendant has really given me extra energy and had boosted my performance as well as elevate my confidence to score goals.</description><keyword>Safee Sali, Malaysia, National Football Team Striker, Malaysian Super League Season, International Matches, National Team,  Quantum Pendant.</keyword><robots>all</robots><author>klhunter</author></meta><alt_title></alt_title></en><bm><title>Testimonial - Quantum Pendant</title><content></content><meta><description>As a football striker FusionExcel's Quantum Pendant has really given me extra energy and had boosted my performance as well as elevate my confidence to score goals.</description><keyword>Safee Sali, Malaysia, National Football Team Striker, Malaysian Super League Season, International Matches, National Team,  Quantum Pendant.</keyword><robots>all</robots><author>klhunter</author></meta><alt_title></alt_title></bm><chi><title>Testimonial - Quantum Pendant</title><content></content><meta><description>As a football striker FusionExcel's Quantum Pendant has really given me extra energy and had boosted my performance as well as elevate my confidence to score goals.</description><keyword>Safee Sali, Malaysia, National Football Team Striker, Malaysian Super League Season, International Matches, National Team,  Quantum Pendant.</keyword><robots>all</robots><author>klhunter</author></meta><alt_title></alt_title></chi></article>
