<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<article><en><title>Former Baseball Star, Bobby Bradley's Testimonial.</title><content>&lt;table background="img/testimonial_bg.jpg" border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" style="color: rgb(0, 0, 0); font-family: Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 14px; text-align: justify; background-color: rgb(238, 240, 252); " width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr bgcolor="#EEF0FC"&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="10"&gt;
				&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td align="center" valign="top" width="300"&gt;
								&lt;img border="0" height="389" src="http://www.fusionexcel.com/imgnews/testimonial_bobby.jpg" width="276" /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td height="10" width="100%"&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td class="content" height="10" style="font-size: 13px; "&gt;
				In 1999, I was the first round draft pick for the Pittsburgh Pirates. After playing 7 seasons in professional baseball, I tallied up 5 surgeries, 2 herniated disks, nerve damage, and 14 surgical scars. To say the least, I was beat up and knocked out. I took a year off from any form of competition to let my body recover from the aches and pains. In the middle of 2007, I decided to pick up the sport of Long Drive Golf. I made it to the World Championships but was still feeling terrible after the tournaments. My neck was killing me and my right hand was practically closed caused from nerve damage. I was fortunate enough to meet Lance Reader, the owner of Krank golf and also a Long Drive Professional. He introduced me to the Fusion Excel Quantum Pendant along with a couple of exercises. After all of about 30 seconds, I asked him if this pendant had some form of voodoo . It was amazing how much stronger and flexible I was by putting this in my hands. When I show people the pendant or the bracelet they start laughing and say it&amp;#39;s the craziest thing they&amp;#39;ve ever seen. You don&amp;#39;t even need a sales pitch. The pendant does all the selling for you. I wear the pendant everyday and feel totally rejuvenated. The everyday aches and pains are long gone and I&amp;#39;ve already qualified for the 2008 REMAX World Championships with the FusionExcel Quantum Pendant on my neck.&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</content><meta><description>The pendant does all the selling for you. I wear the pendant everyday and feel totally rejuvenated.</description><keyword>Former Baseball Star, Bobby Bradley's Testimonial, Pittsburgh Pirates, Long Drive Golf, World Championships, Krank golf, Long Drive Professional, REMAX World Championships, Quantum Pendant.</keyword><robots>all</robots><author>klhunter</author></meta><alt_title></alt_title></en><bm><title>Congratulations to All FE Achievers at Our Achievers Recognition Dinner!</title><content></content><meta><description>Congratulations to All FE Achievers at Our Achievers Recognition Dinner!</description><keyword>Congratulations to All FE Achievers at Our Achievers Recognition Dinner!</keyword><robots>all</robots><author>klhunter</author></meta><alt_title></alt_title></bm><chi><title>Congratulations to All FE Achievers at Our Achievers Recognition Dinner!</title><content></content><meta><description>Congratulations to All FE Achievers at Our Achievers Recognition Dinner!</description><keyword>Congratulations to All FE Achievers at Our Achievers Recognition Dinner!</keyword><robots>all</robots><author>klhunter</author></meta><alt_title></alt_title></chi></article>
