<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<article>
	<en>
		<title><![CDATA[FE Sponsors RM 36,000 Towards World Lupus Day 2011 'Walkathon-a-Payung'!]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[<p>
	FusionExcel is pleased to sponsor RM 100,000 (comprising of cash &amp; Quantum Science products) towards the Red Tomato Loving Lantern Festival 2011.</p>
<div>
	&nbsp;</div>
<div>
	The Event held on 16th September 2011 saw a gathering of more than 2,000 visitors to the booths located outside Bukit Jalil Stadium. VIPs that attended the event includes YB Puan Teresa Kok Suh Sim (Member of Parliament for Seputeh), Puan Sri Susan Cheah (EXCO member of Sunway Group) and Dato&#39; Nelson Kwok (Founder of Nelson Group) to name a few. Local artistes and celebrities who were invited to perform include supermodels Amber Chia and Wilson Tan, Miss Malaysia World 2008 Soo Wincci, Miss Malaysia World 2009 Thanuja Anathan, Miss Malaysia World 2011 Chloe Chen, Miss Malaysia World 2011 1st Runner Up Pamela Tam and Miss Malaysia World 2011 2nd Runner Up Chua Yee See.</div>
<div>
	&nbsp;</div>
<div>
	FusionExcel was represented by its Founder Director Mr KS Lee, its Event Manager Mr Patrick Chan, its &quot;Hope For Children&quot; Ambassador Ms Maggie Loo, Presidential Director Chow Chong Seng, Presidential Director Loh Chow Huat and their team and Director Leader SP Wong.</div>
<div>
	&nbsp;</div>
<div>
	The main objective of the Event was to raise fund for charities like single mothers, orphanages, special kids and polio patients. At the same time, it also seeks to create a platform for young students, young couples and young working adults to bring their parents to enjoy and celebrate the Mooncake Lantern festival together with Red Tomato newspaper.</div>
<div>
	&nbsp;</div>
<div>
	To encourage young Malaysians to always think positively when they encounter problems in their life, there were sharings by invited artistes Amber Chia and Wilson Tan as well as FusionExcel&#39;s Presidential Director Michael Chong Chee Kheong and Presidential Director Ngoh Kwee Lang who talked about their ups and downs in life.</div>
<div>
	&nbsp;</div>
<div>
	On behalf of FusionExcel, Founder Director Mr KS Lee presented a special gift of appreciation to YB Puan Teresa Kok. Founder Director Mr KS Lee also presented a mock cheque of RM 100,000 which was received on behalf by Red Tomato&#39;s Group Excutive Chairman Mr. Gan Chin Kew.&nbsp;</div>
<div>
	&nbsp;</div>
<div>
	A charity fashion parade was held towards the end of the Event to raise aditional funds for charities. These items were sponsored by FusionExcel and showcased during a catwalk by Miss Malaysia World 2009 Thanuja Anathan, Miss Malaysia World 2011 Chloe Chen, 1st runner Up Pamela Tam and 2nd Runner Up Chua Yee See.&nbsp;</div>
]]></content>
		<meta>
			<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
			<keyword><![CDATA[]]></keyword>
			<robots><![CDATA[]]></robots>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
		</meta>
	</en>
	<bm>
		<title><![CDATA[Bahasa Melayu]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[]]></content>
		<meta>
			<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
			<keyword><![CDATA[]]></keyword>
			<robots><![CDATA[]]></robots>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
		</meta>
	</bm>
	<chi>
		<title><![CDATA[»ªÓï]]></title>
		<content><![CDATA[]]></content>
		<meta>
			<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
			<keyword><![CDATA[]]></keyword>
			<robots><![CDATA[]]></robots>
			<author><![CDATA[]]></author>
		</meta>
	</chi>
</article>