<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?><article><en><title>FusionExcel Sponsors RM 6,000 Zero Crime Campaign 2009!</title><content>&lt;table border=&quot;0&quot; cellpadding=&quot;0&quot; cellspacing=&quot;0&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td&gt;
				&lt;div align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
					&lt;img src=&quot;http://fusionexcel.com/imgnews/spn_zero_crime.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td class=&quot;content&quot;&gt;
				&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;strong&gt;REPORT BY ANDREW LEONG, CHEK QUEN DO CLUB.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;br /&gt;
				The Year 2009 is a difficult year for the world&amp;#39;s economy with the failure of many U.S. financial institutions that carries global effects. With more workers being retrenched, crimes such as snatching, robbery, thief and rape cases will increase due to financial and mental pressure.&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;br /&gt;
				As the leading organization in crime prevention and self protection through martial art learning, Chek Quen Do Club partnering with FusionExcel will carry out this Zero Crime Campaign 2009 to help reduce crime during this period because we always believe that most criminal incidents can be prevented.&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;strong&gt;Among The Activities Of The Zero Crime Campaign 2009 Are:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;br /&gt;
				- Free talks at schools, institutions of higher learning, private companies and CQD associates.&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;br /&gt;
				- Full day courses for public to acquire knowledge on self-defense.&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;br /&gt;
				- School holiday camp for adolescents.&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;br /&gt;
				- Stage performances and demonstrations at public areas such as shopping malls and company&lt;br /&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;functions.&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;br /&gt;
				- Zero Crime Campaign 2009 Tee Shirt wearing drive.&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;br /&gt;
				- Open classes for children and adults to master techniques of practical self-defense.&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;br /&gt;
				With this sponsorship by FusionExcel, we are able to carry out this campaign and help those who participated. We hope more organizations will take part to realize our goal of improving individual&amp;#39;s awareness and ability to protect our own safety. A thousand thanks to FusionExcel!&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
</content><meta><description>FusionExcel Sponsors RM 6,000 Zero Crime Campaign 2009!</description><keyword>FusionExcel, RM 6,000 Zero Crime Campaign 2009, Report By Andrew Leong, Chek Quen Do Club, U.S. Financial Institutions, snatching, robbery, thief, rape cases, financial and mental pressure, schools, institutions, higher learning, private companies, CQD associates, self-defense, Zero Crime Campaign 2009 Tee Shirt.</keyword><robots>all</robots><author>klhunter</author></meta></en><bm><title>FusionExcel Sponsors RM 6,000 Zero Crime Campaign 2009!</title><content></content><meta><description>FusionExcel Sponsors RM 6,000 Zero Crime Campaign 2009!</description><keyword>FusionExcel, RM 6,000 Zero Crime Campaign 2009, Report By Andrew Leong, Chek Quen Do Club, U.S. Financial Institutions, snatching, robbery, thief, rape cases, financial and mental pressure, schools, institutions, higher learning, private companies, CQD associates, self-defense, Zero Crime Campaign 2009 Tee Shirt.</keyword><robots>all</robots><author>klhunter</author></meta></bm><chi><title>FusionExcel Sponsors RM 6,000 Zero Crime Campaign 2009!</title><content></content><meta><description>FusionExcel Sponsors RM 6,000 Zero Crime Campaign 2009!</description><keyword>FusionExcel, RM 6,000 Zero Crime Campaign 2009, Report By Andrew Leong, Chek Quen Do Club, U.S. Financial Institutions, snatching, robbery, thief, rape cases, financial and mental pressure, schools, institutions, higher learning, private companies, CQD associates, self-defense, Zero Crime Campaign 2009 Tee Shirt.</keyword><robots>all</robots><author>klhunter</author></meta></chi></article>