<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<article>
	<en>
		<title>How To Take Water Crystal Pictures How The Photographs Are Taken</title>
		<content>&lt;p&gt;
	&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" style="color: rgb(0, 0, 0); font-family: Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; text-align: justify; background-color: rgb(238, 240, 252); " width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr align="center" valign="top"&gt;
			&lt;td&gt;
				&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td align="right" valign="top"&gt;
								&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
				&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td width="175"&gt;
								&lt;div align="left"&gt;
									&lt;img height="210" src="http://fusionexcel.com/imgnews/product_howwatercrystal3.jpg" width="173" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
									&lt;span class="smallhead" style="font-size: 11px; font-weight: bold; "&gt;&lt;span class="style13" style="font-size: 10.5px; "&gt;Photographing Inside a Refrigerated Room Set At -5&amp;deg;C.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
									&lt;br /&gt;
									&lt;img height="133" src="http://fusionexcel.com/imgnews/product_howwatercrystal1.jpg" width="173" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
									&lt;span class="style13" style="font-size: 10.5px; "&gt;Playing Music To The Water.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
									&lt;br /&gt;
									&lt;img height="130" src="http://fusionexcel.com/imgnews/product_howwatercrystal2.jpg" width="173" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
									&lt;span class="style13" style="font-size: 10.5px; "&gt;Showing &amp;quot;Thank You&amp;quot; In Japanese To The Water.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
							&lt;td width="10"&gt;
								&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
							&lt;td valign="top"&gt;
								&lt;div align="justify" class="content" style="text-align: justify; "&gt;
									A crystal is a solid substance with orderly configured atoms and molecules. In particular, because snow is formed under a variety of conditions, there are no two crystals that have the same face (just like human faces). Dr. Emoto wondered if this is also the same with the crystal structures of the various types of water on the earth. Dr. Emoto then came up with a theory that when a water molecule crystallizes, pure water becomes a pure crystal. But contaminated water may not crystallize as beautifully as pure water.&lt;br /&gt;
									&lt;br /&gt;
									Water changes rapidly and is unstable. In order to obtain an example of an average crystal, as many samples as possible had to be photographed under as many conditions as possible. It was impossible to obtain identical crystal pictures. In other words, it was impossible to perfectly reproduce the same crystal twice. However, what we did find is that crystals do show a certain distinctive tendency called a grid crystal or laminar crystal structure. Crystals can be identified by this structural tendency.&lt;br /&gt;
									&lt;br /&gt;
									High-speed photography of crystals formed in frozen water reveals changes in the same body of water after specific, concentrated thoughts were directed toward it. Small amounts of water (an 8 oz. glass) as well as large areas of water (such as dams and lakes) were used in these experiments and in all cases the water samples reflected a molecular change.&lt;br /&gt;
									&lt;br /&gt;
									Music and visual images were used to stimulate the water samples. The water was also exposed to words written on paper and photographs placed underneath or around the glass containers to see if these energies had any impact. They did.&lt;br /&gt;
									&lt;br /&gt;
									Naturally, since water covers the largest portion of our planet, and comprises the largest percentage of our physical bodies, the impact of our thoughts and feelings will play a large part in the way our environments get created, both globally and personally.&lt;/div&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr valign="top"&gt;
			&lt;td height="10"&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr valign="top"&gt;
			&lt;td&gt;
				&lt;table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0"&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td align="left" height="51" valign="top" width="718"&gt;
								&lt;div align="justify"&gt;
									&lt;strong&gt;Disclaimer:&lt;br /&gt;
									These products are not a medical device, and not intended for use in the diagnosis of disease or other conditions, or in the cure, mitigation, treatment, or prevention of disease.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
		<meta>
			<description></description>
			<keyword></keyword>
			<author></author>
			<robots></robots>
		</meta>
	</en>
	<bm>
		<title>How To Take Water Crystal Pictures How The Photographs Are Taken</title>
		<content></content>
		<meta>
			<description></description>
			<keyword></keyword>
			<author></author>
			<robots></robots>
		</meta>
	</bm>
	<chi>
		<title>How To Take Water Crystal Pictures How The Photographs Are Taken</title>
		<content></content>
		<meta>
			<description></description>
			<keyword></keyword>
			<author></author>
			<robots></robots>
		</meta>
	</chi>
</article>
