<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<article>
	<en>
		<title>Letter Of Appreciation From Judge Lorenzo B Venaracion.</title>
		<content>&lt;table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%"&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr valign="top"&gt;
			&lt;td width="50%"&gt;
				&lt;img height="264" src="http://www.fusionexcel.com/imgnews/letter1.jpg" width="354" /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
			&lt;td align="right"&gt;
				&lt;img height="264" src="http://www.fusionexcel.com/imgnews/manila23.jpg" width="354" /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td width="50%"&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
			&lt;td align="right"&gt;
				&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr valign="top"&gt;
			&lt;td class="content" colspan="2" style="font-family: Verdana, Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; color: rgb(0, 0, 0); text-align: justify; "&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;
					&lt;a href="http://www.onedaypilot.com.my/client/fusionexcel/dev/article.asp?lang=1&amp;amp;category=1&amp;amp;article_id=822&amp;amp;title=Video%20FE%20Sponsors%20the%20Children%20of%20Payatas,%20Philippines."&gt;Video FE Sponsors the Children of Payatas, Philippines&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;
					Dear Mr. Paul Ting:&lt;br /&gt;
					&lt;br /&gt;
					I wish to reiterate my deep appreciation for your donation of Peso 250,000 for the Health/Nutrition/Literacy Program for disadvantaged Payatas children in Quezon City, Metro Manila in the Philippines. &amp;nbsp;This is indeed an &amp;quot;answered prayer&amp;quot; for Soup Kitchen / Light House Center for Children, and you and FusionExcel International are the &amp;quot;Angels of God&amp;quot; being used by our Great God to bless our disadvantaged children. I am also sending the copy of our Official Receipt Number 096 for your record.&lt;br /&gt;
					&lt;br /&gt;
					I wish to inform you also that aside from the Health/Nutrition (feeding) program, our Light House Center for Children is also undertaking the Smarter Program for our student clientele that will enable the parents to create learning environment at home, cultivate passion for learning, motivate kids to love learning and develop excellent study habits intended to train S.T.A.R. Leaders, Smarter, Transformational, Active &amp;amp; Righteous Leaders for our country.&lt;br /&gt;
					&lt;br /&gt;
					Part of your donation will be used to implement this Smarter Program which is integrated in the Elementary and High School Curriculum for SY 2008-09 through the holding of Workshop on May 19th, and for Training the Mentors (Smarter Specialists) set on 20th-22th May 2008 for the members of the faculty of our Praise Emerald International School, the educational component of Soup Kitchen/Lighthouse Center for Children Foundations, Inc.&lt;br /&gt;
					&lt;br /&gt;
					I will submit to you the reports on these forthcoming activities after their conclusion.&amp;nbsp; The report on the Health/Nutrition (Feeding) Program shall also be forwarded to you to show the progress of the program.&lt;br /&gt;
					&lt;br /&gt;
					I wish to reiterate also my deep appreciation for your desire to make this partnership as part of the CSR program of FE International, which is indeed laudable and shall set the pace for other multinational companies in the Philippine business scene to copy and emulate.&lt;br /&gt;
					&lt;br /&gt;
					You have the assurance that our Great God will definitely return to you and to FE International this generosity a thousand fold in some other ways.&amp;nbsp; We are all praying for you and FE International for your investments in the Philippines shall be crowned with success, and that through your leadership, FE International shall attain its global goal of making people all over the world enjoy the health benefits of our products.&lt;br /&gt;
					&lt;br /&gt;
					Thank you very much again, and I pray that God&amp;#39;s Favor and Grace shall be with you always.&lt;br /&gt;
					&lt;br /&gt;
					Sincerely yours,&lt;br /&gt;
					&lt;br /&gt;
					JUDGE LORENZO B. VENERACION.&lt;br /&gt;
					&lt;br /&gt;
					President &amp;amp; Executive Trustee.&lt;br /&gt;
					Soup Kitchen/Lighthouse Center for Children Foundation, Inc.&lt;br /&gt;
					Praise Emerald International. School Foundation, Inc.&lt;br /&gt;
					Charter President, Rotary Club of Quezon City North.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;table border="0" width="100%"&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td&gt;
								&lt;img height="252" src="http://www.fusionexcel.com/imgnews/letter2.jpg" width="336" /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
							&lt;td align="center"&gt;
								&lt;img height="252" src="http://www.fusionexcel.com/imgnews/letter3.jpg" width="180" /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
							&lt;td align="right"&gt;
								&lt;img height="252" src="http://www.fusionexcel.com/imgnews/letter4.jpg" width="180" /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content>
		<meta>
			<description>Judge Lorenzo B Venaracion wrote an Appreciation Letter to Mr. Paul Ting for his donation of Peso 250, 000 for Payatas children.</description>
			<keyword>Mr. Paul Ting, Peso 250,000, Health/Nutrition/Literacy Program, Payatas, Judge Lorenzo B Venaracion</keyword>
			<author>KLHunter</author>
			<robots>all</robots>
		</meta>
		<alt_title></alt_title></en>
	<bm>
		<title>Letter Of Appreciation From Judge Lorenzo B Venaracion.</title>
		<content></content>
		<meta>
			<description>Judge Lorenzo B Venaracion wrote an Appreciation Letter to Mr. Paul Ting for his donation of Peso 250, 000 for Payatas children.</description>
			<keyword>Mr. Paul Ting, Peso 250,000, Health/Nutrition/Literacy Program, Payatas, Judge Lorenzo B Venaracion</keyword>
			<author>KLHunter</author>
			<robots>all</robots>
		</meta>
		<alt_title></alt_title></bm>
	<chi>
		<title>Letter Of Appreciation From Judge Lorenzo B Venaracion.</title>
		<content></content>
		<meta>
			<description>Judge Lorenzo B Venaracion wrote an Appreciation Letter to Mr. Paul Ting for his donation of Peso 250, 000 for Payatas children.</description>
			<keyword>Mr. Paul Ting, Peso 250,000, Health/Nutrition/Literacy Program, Payatas, Judge Lorenzo B Venaracion</keyword>
			<author>KLHunter</author>
			<robots>all</robots>
		</meta>
		<alt_title></alt_title></chi>
</article>
