<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?><article><en><title>Testimonial - Quantum Pendant</title><content>&lt;p&gt;
	&amp;nbsp;Augustin Ngu, Chinese Martial Arts Grandmaster, Canada.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table border=&quot;0&quot; cellpadding=&quot;0&quot; cellspacing=&quot;0&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td class=&quot;content&quot; valign=&quot;top&quot;&gt;
				&lt;table border=&quot;0&quot; cellpadding=&quot;0&quot; cellspacing=&quot;0&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
					&lt;tbody&gt;
						&lt;tr&gt;
							&lt;td width=&quot;10&quot;&gt;
								&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;
							&lt;td&gt;
								&lt;br /&gt;
								&lt;table border=&quot;0&quot; cellpadding=&quot;0&quot; cellspacing=&quot;0&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot;&gt;
									&lt;tbody&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td width=&quot;50%&quot;&gt;
												&lt;img height=&quot;271&quot; src=&quot;http://fusionexcel.com/imgnews/augustin1.jpg&quot; width=&quot;157&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
											&lt;td align=&quot;right&quot; width=&quot;50%&quot;&gt;
												&lt;img height=&quot;271&quot; src=&quot;http://fusionexcel.com/imgnews/augustin2.jpg&quot; width=&quot;500&quot; /&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
											&lt;td class=&quot;content&quot; colspan=&quot;2&quot; height=&quot;10&quot;&gt;
												&lt;span lang=&quot;EN-ZA&quot;&gt;I was introduced to FusionExcel Quantum Pendant about a month ago. I have been suffering from tendonitis in the arm for almost 3 years now. Because I teach and train almost everyday, my body goes through daily wear and tear. I usually have to go for acupuncture frequently to help with the pain but it won&amp;rsquo;t go away. After wearing the FusionExcel&amp;rsquo;s Quantum Pendant, I noticed the pain was substantially reduced after a day or two. I recently was on vacation with the family and pinched my nerve on the back while unloading the luggage due to overstretching. In the past, a pain like this would be very severe and would last for weeks. However, I found the pain was gone after three to four days without having to seek acupuncture treatment. Thank you Fusion Excel!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
												&lt;br /&gt;
												&lt;strong&gt;GRANDMASTER NGU CREDENTIALS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
												&lt;br /&gt;
												Grandmaster Ngu is a highly respected leader and teacher in the martial arts community of North America. Originally a student of White Crane Kung Fu, his thirst for knowledge led him to master three styles: Shaolin White Crane, Wing Chun, and Northern Shaolin Kung Fu. He is committed to educating North Americans on the practices of the East including chi kung and lion and dragon dance. He remains the highest ranking Shaolin White Crane Kung Fu Master in North America.&lt;br /&gt;
												&lt;br /&gt;
												&lt;ul&gt;
													&lt;li&gt;
														Grandmaster 9th Degree conferred and certified by The World Kuoshu Federation in 2008.&lt;/li&gt;
													&lt;li&gt;
														President of the Canadian International Kuoshu Wushu Federation.&lt;/li&gt;
													&lt;li&gt;
														Chairman of the Traditional Wushu Association of Canada.&lt;/li&gt;
													&lt;li&gt;
														Secretary General of Confederation of Canadian Wushu Organizations.&lt;/li&gt;
													&lt;li&gt;
														President of the Shaolin White Crane Kung Fu Society of Canada.&lt;/li&gt;
													&lt;li&gt;
														Certified International Sanshou Judge under International Wushu Federation.&lt;/li&gt;
													&lt;li&gt;
														Director of the Canadian Kung Fu Challenge Tournaments for the past seventeen years.&lt;/li&gt;
													&lt;li&gt;
														Silver Medalist at the 2008 World Traditional Wushu Championship in China for hand forms.&lt;/li&gt;
													&lt;li&gt;
														Most recently, appointed by the World Sanshou King Championship as the Director to promote Sanshou and organize Sanshou team selections in North America.&lt;/li&gt;
												&lt;/ul&gt;
											&lt;/td&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
										&lt;tr&gt;
										&lt;/tr&gt;
									&lt;/tbody&gt;
								&lt;/table&gt;
							&lt;/td&gt;
						&lt;/tr&gt;
					&lt;/tbody&gt;
				&lt;/table&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
</content><meta><description>After wearing the FusionExcel¡¯s Quantum Pendant, I noticed the pain was substantially reduced after a day or two.</description><keyword>Augustin Ngu, Chinese Martial Arts Grandmaster, Canada, martial arts community, North America, White Crane Kung Fu, Shaolin White Crane, Wing Chun, and Northern Shaolin Kung Fu, chi kung, lion and dragon dance.</keyword><robots>all</robots><author>klhunter</author></meta></en><bm><title>Testimonial - Quantum Pendant</title><content></content><meta><description>After wearing the FusionExcel¡¯s Quantum Pendant, I noticed the pain was substantially reduced after a day or two.</description><keyword>Augustin Ngu, Chinese Martial Arts Grandmaster, Canada, martial arts community, North America, White Crane Kung Fu, Shaolin White Crane, Wing Chun, and Northern Shaolin Kung Fu, chi kung, lion and dragon dance.</keyword><robots>all</robots><author>klhunter</author></meta></bm><chi><title>Testimonial - Quantum Pendant</title><content></content><meta><description>After wearing the FusionExcel¡¯s Quantum Pendant, I noticed the pain was substantially reduced after a day or two.</description><keyword>Augustin Ngu, Chinese Martial Arts Grandmaster, Canada, martial arts community, North America, White Crane Kung Fu, Shaolin White Crane, Wing Chun, and Northern Shaolin Kung Fu, chi kung, lion and dragon dance.</keyword><robots>all</robots><author>klhunter</author></meta></chi></article>